I want it to consume me. Here and now.
I want it to consume me. Here and now...
Uh-huh.
Yeah, that's right.
(Merchant Copy)
Item Reservation Form
Botan Kamiina
Those earrings...
Looks like one of our staff
sold them off by mistake.
Yeah.
I just found out myself.
I'm so sorry.
I did my best to warn them.
We get online orders from overseas too,
so our popular items go out of stock fast.
So cute!
Aren't they, though?
Miss RA.
Why don't we get our ears
pierced together and wear these?
Then we'll match.
Should I hold on to these earrings, then?
Yes!
I understand.
Thank you for letting me know.
Botan Kamiina Fully Blossoms When Drunk
Chin-Lan Chang
Yaeka Kitamori
Akane Yusa
Kanade Gujo
Botan Kamiina
Ibuki Tonami
Fully Blossoms
When Drunk
Botan Kamiina
Fully Blossoms
When Drunk
This sure is some cold.
Just call me Somecold L. Jackson.
Samuel?
Call me Some Peckinpah.
I Am Some.
Some 41!
Hodosan Ropeway
Hodo-Sanroku Station
Put a sock in it.
Oh, there's no one here yet.
Let me use the restroom.
Oh, me too.
Amazake
Roasted Ginkgo Nuts
from Chichibu
It's still dark out.
Will we be able to see them?
Pay for items at cashier counter
Alcoholic Drinks
Huh? See what?
Look at this. They sell booze here.
Pay for items at cashier counter
Alcoholic Drinks
Miss RA, you're not much
of a team player, are you?
Wh-Why do you say that?!
I hope we get to see some good clouds.
Same here.
I have high hopes based on the big swings
in daily temperature we've had lately.
See, there's what we call
radiative cooling...
Hodosan Ropeway
Dispenses pointless trinkets not pictured here!
"Dispenses pointless trinkets"...
No returns, refunds, or exchanges.
"No returns, refunds, or exchanges."
Dispenses pointless trinkets not pictured here!
No returns, refunds, or exchanges.
Surprise Box
That's a lot of warnings.
I wonder how long they've been here.
Right?
Also...
Mt. Hodo Rope (Large)
(After tax)
I was surprised to see that they
sell rope from the ropeway here.
Can't believe you can even buy the rope.
Hey.
They've opened the ropeway.
All right.
Isn't it kinda scary when you
pass under a ropeway tower?
The way it lurches reminds me
of an amusement park ride.
It's like the sky and mountains
have melted into one...
A sight you can only see in winter.
This brief moment in time...
It's really something special.
Panorama Map
I don't see anything.
What?
Is this thing broken?
What are the chances?
Did you put any coins in?
Ah!
Hey, now.
Mt. Hodo (497.1m)
Environment Agency, Saitama Prefecture
This is the summit?
Even with the sun shining
down, it's so chilly.
Hey, Senpai.
If we hold hands, we can stay warm.
Something wrong with your hand?
Nope.
Just that...
It feels a little cold and empty
this time of year.
Once it gets warmer, the plum blossoms
and fukujuso should bloom, at least.
That's because your shoulders are exposed.
You can wear my jacket.
No, thanks.
Then you'll be cold instead.
In that case, how about we share a drink?
Chichibu Umezake
I bought this Buko umeshu
before we came up here.
It's delicious and'll warm you right up.
Thanks.
Botan?
Ibuki?
Ibuki!
Check it out, Botan!
Winter cherry blossoms!
See? Winter's not so empty, is it?
Yeah. You're right.
It's almost Christmas.
Any Christmas Eve plans?
Spending it alone.
That's too sad! Let's get a group going!
Awesome!
How festive of a holiday is it in Japan?
Something like the Mid-Autumn Festival?
I've never even heard
of the Mid-Autumn Festival.
What?
Christmas in Taiwan
isn't the same as Japan?
Not at all.
It's a 360-degree difference!
You know that's a full circle.
Do families eat cake together?
Nope.
What about couples swapping gifts?
No way! Bô—lah!
Huh, it's nothing like Japan.
Told you.
A drab, colorless Christmas.
You think?
Sorry that I keep dragging you
to the bookstore, by the way.
I don't mind. It's fun.
What are you here to buy?
A Foucault book translated into Japanese
for the first time, as well as...
something to read over winter break.
This author has a new book out?
Another hefty one, I see!
You really like books, huh?
Mm.
It's settled.
Huh?
Let's do a gift swap. With books.
Wh-Why?
For Christmas!
Isn't that what couples do here?
30 Minutes
We'll each pick a book in thirty minutes,
then meet up at the café outside.
I'm scared that no matter what I choose,
I'll end up swinging and missing!
Or should I stop selfishly trying for
home runs when it comes to prestations?
Wait, "prestation"? Just call it a gift!
Who am I, Mauss?
I'm deflecting...
And isn't it arrogant to be like,
"I hope it makes her happy" to begin with?
That said, it's hard to choose a book
without that mindset.
I can't even tell if I'm thinking about
the books or about Chin-Lan anymore.
"There is nothing in all the world
that is ever once and simply resolved."
Hideo Kobayashi was right
on the money with that one.
I want to know more about her.
The one I got...
is this!
It's like an anthology
of contemporary Taiwanese poetry.
Chen Li's an interesting poet.
I hope you like it.
Thanks.
Um, do you like poetry?
I don't know much about it, but yes.
Here are your drinks.
I watched a movie about
Taiwanese poets way back when.
It was the first time I really thought
about Japan's influence on Taiwan.
And just earlier, that memory
suddenly came rushing back to me.
I want to show you more of
those parts of me, Kanade.
I may not be very good at talking
about myself or my feelings...
But here.
A photography book?
Actually...
Picture postcards...
They're postcards of photos taken
by one of my favorite movie directors.
If you'd like,
one day...
I'd love it if you'd write about yourself
and send them to me,
Chin-Lan.
Yes, I will.
Botan Kamiina
Fully Blossoms
When Drunk
Botan Kamiina
Fully Blossoms
When Drunk
Botan Kamiina
Fully Blossoms
When Drunk
Botan Kamiina
Fully Blossoms
When Drunk
Look at that pesky snow coming down.
I wonder if Echigo-Yuzawa gets as much
snow buildup as Tateyama-Sanroku.
Now then, Botan.
I'll be the one taking
the lead for this trip.
Okay?
Echigo-Yuzawa Station
Yes, I can't wait.
Nothing says Niigata like rice!
Nothing says rice like sake!
And nothing says sake like Ponshukan!
What is Ponshukan, you ask?
A specialty food shop selling all sorts of
Niigata specialties new even to locals!
There's even a sake bath of Echigo-Yuzawa
hot spring water blended with sake.
Ponshukan
Kikizake
Bansho
And at Kikizake Bansho, you can try sake
samples from all of Niigata's breweries.
Isn't it wonderful?
Ponshukan
I've always wanted to come here!
They sell Ponshukan-exclusive
sakes here, too!
She's really enjoying herself.
Why did I just feel a wave of relief?
Did I force you
into coming out here?
Let's check it out already!
It always comes back to alcohol.
Botan?
Breweries of Echigo
Kikizake Bansho
Echigo-Yuzawa Station Branch
Th-There must be a hundred kinds here!
What? These are all sake from Niigata?
Some of these sake cost multiple
of these coins we just bought.
Um, I'll go with this one. Kaganoi.
Wait, that was fast! Why that one?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Ponshukan Benchmark Sake
This sake is the benchmark for Kikizake
Bansho by which we grade flavors using
stars, as well as our own comments.
We hope it can serve as a reference
for your sake tasting.
It says this sake is the benchmark used to
compare flavors for all the other sake.
What? Then I pick that one, too.
Looks like someone's a copycat.
Which one should I try next?
I still have some left, so you
can look by yourself, Ibuki.
Sure!
It's delicious.
Drinking sake standing up,
like it's coffee from a vending machine.
Would I ever have done this
if I hadn't met Ibuki?
Botan!
We should come back here again.
And when we do...
Let's try all the ones they have together!
Okay?
Sounds good.
They were selling masu cups outside...
How many years will that take?
By then, we might not
be in college anymore.
Why, we might not even
be living in the dorm.
How many times are left
for us to drink together?
Matsukaze - Seven
Please enjoy your stay with us.
What a lovely room!
Don't you think, Ibuki?
Two beer bottles, cola, and club soda!
Wow!
The fridge is full of so many
complimentary drinks!
Menacing
Are you listening?
Yeah! Sorry!
I-I love how big these windows are!
Let's start by putting
the beer bottle down.
The beds are pushed together!
Kinda naughty, if you ask me.
Huh?
What is it?
You're so cute, Ibuki.
W-We have some time until dinner.
Wanna check out the big bath?
Nuh-uh.
I'd rather be alone with you.
I want...
to go further.
Can I?
I'll only ask once.
No more after that.
Um, wait...
I'm not ready to...
Not ready?
I see now.
So I was the only one ready?
Ibuki.
You and I...
We stopped being friends,
so what are we now?
What?
These are... How?
She said these earrings were sold out.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I made you worry again.
I was the one
who bought them a while back.
But I couldn't work up the courage...
Why did...
Take this...
and pierce my ear.
I wanted you to be the one to do it.
Before we went any further.
And, if you'd like, um...
Of course.
Do me as well.
Dorm Group Chat (6)
Just a little past Hanno now. We ate in Ikebukuro,
so we'll be heading straight home.
Chin-Lan
I understand
Kanade
Have a safe trip back
Yaeka
I bet you forgot, but we're cleaning up
the entire dorm tomorrow.
Wait, we are?
Yaeka
I bet you forgot, but we're cleaning up
the entire dorm tomorrow.
Wait, we are?
Yaeka
That's the same thing Akane said...
I bet you forgot, but we're cleaning up
the entire dorm tomorrow.
Wait, we are?
Yaeka
That's the same thing Akane said...
Akane
Yeah, and?
Drool...
We can talk about the clean-up once we get back.
I'll let you know when we're at the station.
I knew that the beds
would be pushed together.
What?
I mean, I was the one
who made the reservation.
How naughty.
Huh?
Does it hurt?
No, it feels fine now.
And you?
Same here.
Six weeks for the starter earring...
I said I'm sorry.
We can change them out together
when the time comes.
Yeah.
Besides...
We bought some liquor
that'll take even longer.
Reservation Certificate
Ibuki Tonami    Botan Kamiina
We have received your reservation for the memorial shochu Menko Mirai.
It will be kept safe in our dedicated room-temperature
storage space until the delivery date.
Receiving Party
Botan Kamiina
Sending Party
Ibuki Tonami
They'll keep it in storage
for up to five years.
By then, we might be living
far apart from each other...
We won't be apart.
What?
Let's make sure we're not, Botan.
I'm feeling a little thirsty.
Why don't we have a drink?
Translation: John K.
Editing & Typesetting: Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing: Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check: Alicia Ashby
Translation Check: Sriram Gurunathan