(Today's Handsome Heritage)
(Cultural heritage in South Chungcheong Province)
(Lean and handsome Jae Hyeon appears as a guest.)
(He decided on his team members before coming.)
(Reattempt cards)
(Jae Hyeon picks Team Old Boy Handsome in high spirits.)
(Acting like they already won)
(Identification card, 30-minute nap card...)
(Team Young Boy Guys without reattempt cards)
(Jealous)
(Reattempt cards with power?)
(We'll win the bingo no matter what.)
(The spot in Cheonan)
(The spot in Cheonan is here?)
(The war starts right away.)
(Team Handsome gets ahead thanks to quick Jae Hyeon.)
(However, they aren't good at quizzes.)
(Reattempt card)
(Using a reattempt card right away)
(They keep getting wrong answers.)
(They use up all the reattempt cards and get more stressed out.)
(Reattempt card)
(Our theme for today)
(Team Guys shouts for no stress.)
(Thanks to their positive attitude)
That's correct.
(Smoothly answering correctly)
(Both teams rush over...)
(to Nonsan.)
(During their race towards Nonsan,)
(they arrive before Team Handsome.)
(Team Handsome is no longer in the lead.)
That's correct.
(Team Guys is unstoppable.)
(Even the birthday girl came into the bakery.)
(Their mission was cleared easily.)
(No stress)
(Current score)
(Will Team Guys with no stress win?)
Wait.
Instead of getting lost in joy,
we need to make a plan.
- All right.
- What should we do?
Shall we check their location now?
Let's use the identification card...
to decide our next destination.
- We should find out their location.
- No stress.
(Team Handsome in Cheonan)
(Where did they go after Cheonan?)
We'd like to find out.
We'll use our identification card.
We'd like to find out where they are.
- Just leave it.
- Leave it?
The message is here.
(Team Handsome at Buyeo National Museum)
- Gosh.
- They arrived.
They're inside the museum.
- See that?
- Where?
Gilt-bronze Incense Burner. Wait.
They're at Buyeo A.
- A?
- Yes.
We need to go now.
- Right now...
- In this case,
we should go to Seosan.
(Seosan: Rock-Carved Triad Buddha)
They can block us and win this square at the same time.
- We need to block Seosan.
- You're right.
(Blocking each other's bingo)
This is what happened.
So it's about who wins the most again, right?
(Entering a long match)
Seosan is right here.
We can go to Buyeo B.
- Why?
- After Buyeo B...
- We shouldn't go to Buyeo B.
- No?
- Here's why.
- If we go there,
they would get so angry.
Sang Uk, we have to go to Seosan no matter what.
- We do?
- We aren't in a hurry,
but we should go to Seosan now.
Can you search Seosan?
Goodbye.
- Thank you.
- Have a good day.
(After wishing happy birthday and coming up with a plan)
I'll drive.
No, I'm okay for now.
- But we're going to Seosan.
- It's okay.
(Team Guys sets off to Seosan.)
(But why are we going to Seosan?)
No stress,
but I got stressed out earlier.
I got very stressed out when we mentioned Buyeo B.
I still don't understand.
Wasn't it worth it to consider my suggestion?
No, not at all. That's why I was startled.
Sang Uk, I'll explain again.
- I'll make it simple.
- Okay.
Now that they won Buyeo A,
our bingo line is broken.
- Right?
- Yes.
Let's say that we go to Buyeo B now.
Think about the time we will spend...
on taking the quiz and eating food...
even if it's a dessert.
Once the other team wins Buyeo A,
only Seosan will remain.
- They would go up.
- Once they get there, it's over.
Then we'll be stressed out from then on.
I see.
If they shampoo their hair and sleep...
We wouldn't even get stressed out...
because we'd lose.
- I mean...
- Defeat.
Even if they shampoo their hair and take a nap,
would we still be behind?
We don't need to take those risks.
- Right.
- We don't?
By 12pm, we occupied 2 squares...
and cleared all our missions.
No one has done it faster than us.
That was amazing.
Even the birthday person came in...
so that we could congratulate her.
I'm curious about the next step. After Seosan...
If we come back down,
we'll have to drive another 100km.
Right.
(From Seosan to Buyeo B)
- Yi Kyung.
- I'll drive later.
- No stress.
- Right, no stress.
You didn't get stressed out just now, right?
No, I got stressed out about Buyeo B.
(He's tired of hearing it.)
While making plans,
one of us kept saying, "What about Buyeo B?"
Apologize to me now.
All right.
Hey, why would you apologize?
I said it with a lingering feeling.
Buyeo B, apologize.
Buyeo B.
It was very difficult. The opposing team...
(Cuckoo)
Buyeo A.
- Buyeo A.
Okay, Buyeo A.
(Disappointed)
Buyeo A? Okay.
They will either go to Buyeo B or go north.
(Seosan or Buyeo B)
They'll probably win Buyeo B.
(From Buyeo A to Buyeo B)
While expecting us to block Seosan, they'll go to Buyeo B?
(Team Handsome)
Should we go directly to Seosan?
Look, Tae Hyun.
- By the way...
- We need to think carefully.
Aren't they 100 percent likely to go to Seosan?
They're probably on their way there.
(Dong Hyun is sure that they're on their way to block Seosan.)
I'm 100 percent sure.
I think it's all or nothing.
(Jae Hyeon wants to head to Seosan and win.)
Now that they're notified,
they'll probably put us to sleep.
(7 minutes from Buyeo A to B)
Tae Hyun, it only takes seven minutes to get there.
What do you think about Buyeo B?
- Buyeo B?
- Yes.
Okay, we'll go to Buyeo B.
- All right. Buyeo B?
- Yes.
If the other team is in Buyeo B,
we should go directly to Seosan.
Then bingo will be completed.
All right.
(Dong Hyun came back from the convenience store.)
- Can we eat on our way?
- Yes.
Can I give this to you?
If they came to Buyeo,
they probably would go to Buyeo A.
Right? We'll find out over there.
We'll find out once we get there.
Put your seatbelt on.
(They head to check Buyeo B.)
Tae Hyun.
- There are two types.
- Gosh.
- Thank you. It's warm latte.
- Here you go.
(Anything is good for Tae Hyun who's in a hurry.)
I'll put it right here.
(They finish the eating mission instantly.)
(They arrive quickly.)
It's nearby.
We could have walked here.
Is their car here?
(Looking around)
What?
(Please be here, guys.)
Are they not here?
You don't see their car, do you?
- They're not here.
- No.
They probably didn't come here.
It means that they never planned to come to Buyeo.
(The second location in Buyeo is up to Team Handsome.)
Gosh, what a waste.
Dong Hyun, you got the correct answer in the end.
That's for sure.
Both my shoulders and lower back feel stiff.
If we get it right answer this time,
you'll feel recovered.
- Of course.
- Yes.
It's over there.
So that's it.
There it is.
They made it very big. It's huge.
(There's a high and mysterious stone tower.)
(Five-Story Stone Pagoda)
(Handsome Heritage 3: The Last Days of Baekje)
It must be him.
Hello.
- Hello. Goodness.
- Goodness.
- The ice has melted.
- I see the path ahead of us.
It's covered with mud.
- It's mud.
- We're already in the mud.
It's the path ahead of us.
- Hello. It's him again.
- Hello.
(Surprised)
- What?
Are you in charge of two locations?
(Professor Kim Jae Won they met in the morning)
Do you know what this place is?
I saw that it's called Jeongnimsa Temple.
There's a famous stone pagoda here.
Behind you is Five-Story Stone Pagoda at Jeongnimsa Temple.
This is the site for Jeongnimsa Temple,
which is where the name comes from.
Was it Jeongnimsa Temple in the past?
That's right.
- Gosh, it's huge.
- Isn't it enormous?
- Yes.
- The location is very important.
It's at the center of Baekje's capital city.
Right at the center.
The midpoint of the straight road is...
right here.
(Jeongnimsa Temple was in the middle of the capital city.)
To explain about Jeongnimsa Temple,
I need to talk...
about the history of Baekje.
What was the first capital city of Baekje?
The first capital city was...
It's nearby.
Nearby? No way.
It's very far...
- Baekje's capital city...
- from here.
I forgot.
It's Gangnam.
- Gangnam? Really?
- Gangnam in Seoul.
- Mongchontoseong.
- Right.
That was Baekje's...
It's predicted to be the first capital city...
- of Baekje.
- Really?
That was the first capital city.
Up until then, Baekje was a prosperous kingdom.
- The capital was up north.
- It was quite big.
It was very big,
Baekje had a lot of national strength...
that could compare to Goguryeo.
The most important reason is their diplomacy.
That's right.
You must be aware of it.
Yes, when it comes to diplomacy...
It was good at being diplomatic.
Then a war against Goguryeo got started.
In a way, Baekje was unlucky with the opponents.
- I see.
- At that time,
a famous king was born in Goguryeo.
- Gwanggaeto the Great.
- Yes, that's correct.
After facing Gwanggaeto the Great, Baekje started to wither.
Under King Jangsu's reign, Goguryeo took over the Han River.
Baekje was kicked out.
We can say that Baekje was in ruins at this time.
About 60 years have passed.
Suddenly, a famous king faced a renaissance.
King Seong, the son of King Muryeong,
suggested moving.
- That's how Sabi was chosen.
- Sabi.
(Changing the capital to Sabi in 583, which is now Buyeo)
It was where...
Baekje was revitalized.
- Let's take a look at the pagoda.
- Sure.
Has it not changed at all since then?
The pagoda hasn't changed.
Only two stone pagodas from Baekje remain.
This is one of them.
This is so impressive.
It's been 1,000 years.
(Five-Story Stone Pagoda at Jeongnimsa Temple)
It's a pagoda made with stone.
Do you notice anything strange in the shape?
- In the shape?
- Yes.
Isn't this how it's usually shaped?
- The ends are...
- Right.
(Underneath the eave is pointing up.)
What's the difference?
As a stone pagoda, this is quite big.
- The size?
- It's very big.
Also, the shape... Can you name a pagoda...
that you're familiar with?
- Dabotap.
- Seokgatap.
Those are a few.
This was built earlier than those.
Based on its shape,
it's been influenced by wooden pagodas.
After seeing wooden pagodas in China,
they thought of making one with stone.
That's why it looks like something...
in between a stone pagoda and a wooden pagoda.
After the fall of Baekje,
this is one of the very few pagodas...
from Baekje that remain now.
It's a very precious cultural heritage.
There are only a few.
Making the ends like this...
with stone isn't easy.
- How did they build it?
- I know.
(Buyeo B: Five-Story Stone Pagoda at Jeongnimsa Temple)
Please, let's get one more question.
(Time for Quiz)
During the Baekje period...
- What? Baekje period?
- Yes.
During the Baekje period, paper was rare.
- What was rare?
- Paper.
- Paper?
- Yes, paper was rare.
We have to listen carefully.
Mokgan was often used,
which is writing on a piece of wood.
I saw this.
Me too. I remember it.
The mokgan in the photo was found...
- We saw it earlier.
- on the site in Sabi...
in 2011.
It was made to study this. What could it be?
How is this possible?
- I know the answer.
- We won.
Wait a minute.
Why does it always happen...
when we don't have any reattempt cards?
- Shall we answer it simultaneously?
- Shall we?
We weren't being filmed at that time.
- Right.
- We weren't being filmed.
- Really?
- We weren't.
- We just...
- The curator told us.
(1 hour ago at Buyeo National Museum)
I know them all. King Seong, King Beop,
King Hye, King Mu, and King Uija.
What's this?
It's multiplication table mokgan.
- What?
- Multiplication table.
Such relics were found in Buyeo.
During Baekje before the year 1400.
Why?
They show that...
people knew numbers and multiplication back then.
(Did they memorize this back then?)
Did they memorize this back then?
(Winner Team Handsome is bound to win.)
(Shall we say it in the count of three?)
- Why did this come up when...
- By the way,
are you sure?
- I'm sure.
- Tae Hyun.
Let's take a look.
Are you sure?
It was written on the others next to it.
Weren't there three of them?
- Yes.
- It was written on here.
- Were they the same?
- Yes.
- Okay, that works.
- Tae Hyun.
- One, two, three. Multiplication.
Correct.
What did I tell you? This is so odd.
When there's no reattempt card,
the brain pulls all the resources from the universe.
Let's see.
- When you look at the front of it, - Right.
it's faint but written in ink.
What you saw earlier...
had been restored with infrared.
I read all of it.
It starts from multiples of nine.
- Where?
- Multiples of nine.
Nine times nine is eighty-one. Seven times nine is sixty-three.
(A long-standing tradition of private education)
From multiples of nine from the top...
- Right.
- If we didn't hear...
his explanation,
- it was impossible to answer it.
- Right.
Multiplication table. One, two.
- Multiplication table.
Tae Hyun.
(Buyeo B: Five-Story Stone Pagoda at Jeongnimsa Temple)
I feel amazing now.
I can't believe the question was on something that we saw.
Without the reattempt card,
you were very careful when listening to the question.
I feel so good.
- Unbelievable.
- Thank you.
It's lotus leaf rice set meal.
- Let's order only one.
- Okay.
Okay, we don't have much time.
We already won three.
- Right, we only need one.
- Wait.
If they don't take away Asan and Yesan...
They won't get the bingo.
- We can also go to Seosan.
- What should we do?
Let's eat first.
We have to take a nap and wash our hair.
- Let's get going.
- Let's go.
Let's go to the restaurant first.
(Team Guys)
We traveled far, and we're almost at Seosan.
Seosan is important.
It will be difficult for us if we don't get Seosan.
We will lose our confidence.
Seosan is the most important spot.
- For both teams.
- Yes.
(Seung Ho notices something at the entrance.)
Gosh, there it is.
He looks very mischievous.
I don't know if I can say this.
Who does?
The middle Buddha statue of Rock-Carved Triad Buddha.
He looks very mischievous. I just saw a photo.
A photo? I thought you could actually see it.
- We're here.
- That was perfect.
Thank you for driving.
We have to get to the other side.
We do? You're right.
This is a hiking special.
There's tourist information on Rock-Carved Triad Buddha.
- The entrance is free.
- You're right.
It's called Seosan City Culture Facilities Administer Office.
National Treasure Number 84.
(Tourist Information on Rock-Carved Triad Buddha)
I see why you called him mischievous.
- I just saw it.
- Right?
Doesn't he look slightly mischievous?
(They hurry over to the Buddha statue that looks mischievous.)
- Mischievous?
- Mischievous.
I'll take a look up there.
(Magnificent features of the mountain come into view.)
The view is beautiful.
(The end of the uphill seems far away.)
It's very steep.
Be careful not to slip.
The energy of victory...
and hunger.
I feel them at the same time.
(Panting)
"My enthusiasm..."
She's waiting for us.
- Here we are.
- Hello.
- We might get it wrong.
- Hello, nice to meet you.
- Hello.
We traveled far to see Rock-Carved Triad Buddha.
Could you explain what it is?
First, we're standing in front of The Gate of Non-Duality.
- "The Gate of Non-Duality?" - Yes.
The Gate of Non-Duality indicates...
that this world is before the gate.
Beyond that gate is the world of Buddha.
It means that we're one with Buddha.
The truth is 1, not 2.
(The Gate of Non-Duality, located between this world...)
(and the world of Buddha)
Shall we go into the world...
- of Buddha?
- Okay.
Shall we go through the Gate of Non-Duality?
- After the gate, it was written...
- Buyeo A.
Please excuse us, ma'am.
How did they get it so quickly?
Now that you think about it, shouldn't we have gone there?
What are you talking about? No.
They have to come up, and we must block them.
- Okay.
- Next...
we'll win this one.
- Let's hurry.
- Let's block them.
- May I take the pamphlet?
- Just take one.
Let's go.
We're in the world of Buddha now.
- Okay.
- From here?
(Handsome Heritage 6, A Smile of 1,000 Years)
We must win this one.
(Panting)
If not, it'll be horrible.
Let's see.
(Rock-Carved Triad Buddha finally appears.)
So this is Rock-Carved Triad Buddha?
You're right.
(Rock-Carved Triad Buddha)
- How did they build this?
- Is this the right way?
This is National Treasure Number 84,
Rock-Carved Triad Buddha in Yonghyeon-ri, Seosan.
When most people hear...
that it's a national treasure, they expect it to be enormous.
They're surprised to see how small it is.
After listening to my explanation,
you'll understand why it's the best rock-carved Buddha statue in Korea.
- Please go ahead.
- Sure.
"Maae" means...
carved rock.
(Carved "ma," rock "ae")
(At the end of Baekje, the statue was made by carving out the rock.)
(Then what is Triad Buddha?)
The first one holding a marble is...
Dipankara, one of Buddhas from the past.
(The first among Triad Buddha, Dipankara)
(Helped Gautama Buddha attain Buddhahood)
- What is he holding?
- Bongboju.
When you die and enter the underworld,
a marble of this size will pivot...
around the life you led.
- Have you heard of that story?
- It's called bongboju.
(Standing in the middle)
On our way here, Seung Ho looked up the photo...
and said that one of them looked mischievous.
Here's the one who looks mischievous.
(You called me mischievous? That's discourteous.)
It's also known as Smile of Baekje.
Among Buddhas,
Siddhartha Gautama attained Buddhahood.
It means the one who's enlightened.
After becoming Buddha, he will lead the way for the sentient beings.
If there are sentient beings that he missed,
Maitreya will appear after 5.67 billion years.
they will lead the way for the missing sentient beings.
They're Triad Buddha of the past, present, and future.
(Maitreya, Buddha of the future, the savior of sentient beings)
The most significant feature is...
the smile.
- The smile?
- Yes.
Think about it. There's no life to rocks.
Because of the smile, it looks alive.
(Smiling for thousands of years without any change)
From the east at 30 degrees,
it looks the most balanced.
When there's proper sunlight,
its mysterious quality can't be described in words.
(As the facial expression changes, it's more mysterious.)
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Thank you.
Take a careful look at it.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
- She explained so well.
Can I read the pamphlet?
Please return it during the quiz.
Then we should read it now.
He won't ask about the shape, will he?
Right, it's in front of us.
It won't come up, right?
- Let's start the quiz.
- Okay.
All right.
You'll be disqualified if you turn around.
Please put it down.
The shape of two hands of the Buddha in the middle...
of Rock-Carved Triad Buddha is different.
The shape on the right means getting rid of all fears of sentient beings.
The shape on the left means granting all wishes of sentient beings.
In the count of three, please make...
the same shape of the Buddha's hands.
You're not allowed to discuss.
This is very difficult.
It was shaped like this.
(A question that they never imagined)
You aren't allowed to discuss.
(A question that they can't even discuss)
(Flustered by the question about the shape)
Close your eyes and imagine it, Sang Uk.
I didn't look at the hands.
How did they look?
Please think quietly.
- Think quietly.
- How can we think quietly?
This is... Wait.
Do we have to guess the fingers too?
Yes, that's the question.
All three of you have to be right.
Guys, I don't know the answer.
Gosh, what was it?
- That's why we can't turn around.
- We lost.
This is all I can think about. I'll go with this.
- Let's just do it.
- All right.
One, two, three.
That's incorrect.
(Incorrect)
Can we take a look now?
What's wrong? Do we get another chance?
I'll give you another chance.
Can we talk about what we did?
You may discuss without turning around.
- This was the right hand.
- You have one more chance.
This was my left hand.
This is what I did.
(This is...)
What about you?
That must be wrong. We were all different.
All of us were different.
This is what I remember,
but I don't know about the fingers.
No, this was the right hand.
- It's the opposite.
- Hey. Darn it.
I don't remember the fingers.
Isn't this too much of Spider Man?
Yi Kyung, was this the shape of the right hand?
- This was the right hand.
- Is this correct?
- Yes.
- I'll believe you.
That can't be it.
It can't be it?
- It looks like Spider Man.
- That's totally off.
It's either this or that.
Why do they both look wrong?
You know, my fingers feel very strange.
I don't feel like they belong to me.
- This question is so hard.
- They don't feel like my fingers.
- What's your guess, Sang Uk?
- Mine is this.
- Let's think about it.
- This?
- All fingers are extended?
- It's because...
This is my guess.
This is mine.
- This?
- I think this is it.
- How about rock-paper-scissors?
- We're all different.
- All our guesses are different.
- Right.
- The answer must be one of these.
- I agree.
Let's do this.
We'll go with mine.
If one of you is correct,
one of you will go home.
- The remaining two will decide.
- If one of us is correct?
- Yes, what do you think?
- We'll go.
- Okay.
Make the shape of the Buddha's hands.
- We'll go with this.
- One, two, three.
Hold that pose.
Two of you will turn around and check.
This is so...
- Wait, I can't look.
- Wait.
Isn't this a punishment?
If we get it wrong,
you should stay like this and become the fourth Buddha.
Two of you, please turn around.
- It's not clear.
- What?
Isn't this it?
May I turn around?
This is it.
- All of us were wrong.
- We were wrong.
Is this it?
- Is this it?
- Yes, that's it.
Hey, we were all wrong.
We were all wrong.
So that's the pose?
(Gosh, you've been mischievous with us.)
I didn't even imagine that it would be this pose.
- Seriously.
- I did the pose at one point.
I didn't even imagine it.
- Seriously.
- I did the pose at one point.
If someone had come up with this...
We'd say, "Are you shooting a gun?"
- Right?
- Right.
We were right about this.
Two of them were open.
He kept saying that two were open.
- So this is it.
- When Dong Hyun comes here,
he has more chance of getting it right than us.
He keeps looking for strange details.
We'd better hurry and leave.
They're definitely on their way here.
Yesan A?
What if they come to Seosan and get it wrong?
- Then we'll go to Asan.
- And we win Asan.
We have a chance of winning.
They could possibly get it wrong.
- Gosh.
- This was difficult.
I guarantee you that they won't get it right.
The number of fingers that are extended...
This isn't easy. We'll go to Yesan A.
Put them to sleep and go to Asan.
(Team Handsome)
Excuse me.
Can we get...
- Two lotus leaf rice, please.
- two lotus leaf rice?
He will definitely order tteokgalbi.
I'll cover tteokgalbi.
- You're covering...
- We have to do it.
Good job.
Sir, when someone asks about tteokgalbi,
could you tell him that it's sold out?
- I will.
- Thank you.
(He's coming.)
After going to Seosan,
we can head to Asan.
There's only an hour difference.
- We already ordered.
- Okay.
- They only have lotus leaf rice.
- Right.
How is it so famous?
I'm curious.
The restaurant only sells...
lotus leaf rice.
There's nothing to eat other than lotus leaf rice.
- I heard that it was incredible.
- Really?
- I'm curious.
- Don't be curious.
(Giggling)
- There's nothing else on the menu?
- No.
(Laughing)
- There's nothing else on the menu?
- No.
There should be something to go with rice.
There isn't anything.
- There isn't anything.
- What's this?
- There's nothing.
- There's tteokgalbi.
Of course, there's tteokgalbi.
No way.
- It's because...
- It's sold out.
There must be meat to go with lotus leaf rice.
No, forget it.
- What else is there?
- No.
Of course there's something else on the menu.
That's hilarious.
It's okay. I ate a lot earlier.
(Tae Hyun calls someone.)
Who are you calling? The hair salon?
This is the hair salon.
Ma'am, are you open right now?
- Yes.
- How much is it...
to get the hair shampooed?
- Shampooing is ten dollars.
- Shampoo?
Shampooing for ten dollars? Okay.
We'll get there within 15 minutes.
There's someone...
who made a reservation.
While you take care of your client's hair,
can we get our hair shampooed...
I can shampoo your hair.
We also have someone who can shampoo my hair.
- You want to wash yourself?
- Yes.
We can do it ourselves.
It's possible...
as long as you let us use your facility.
Oh, okay.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Bye.
(They haven't heard anything from Team Guys.)
They must be heading to Seosan.
They definitely went north.
Considering that they're taking a long time.
In order to block us,
- they have to go to Seosan.
- Exactly.
(The food is finally served.)
By the way...
- There's a lot of food.
- I know.
- Hey.
- Isn't it that?
Freshwater snails.
It's also served with mackerel.
Thank you.
The food is nicely presented.
Food for the well-being.
(Shall we try the lotus leaf rice set meal?)
It's 30 minutes.
- Let's leave in ten minutes.
- Okay.
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food.
- Enjoy.
This is fascinating. It's nicely served.
It's fascinating.
(Opening up the lotus leaf)
(Dong Hyun smells it first.)
The herbal medicine at a sauna...
It has the smell of a sauna.
- Herbal medicine?
- Herbal medicine.
The smell is nice.
It smells healthy.
Why is this neighborhood known for lotus leaves?
At the Gungnamji Pond,
about ten million lotus flowers bloom.
(Exclaiming)
Gungnamji Pond in this neighborhood?
(Real and natural lotus flowers)
It's a natural lotus leaf.
- It's glutinous rice.
- Yes.
(Dong Hyun tries the glutinous rice first.)
(The essence of lotus leaf rice)
It's steamed.
(Jae Hyeon also tries a bite.)
- By the way...
- The rice tastes amazing.
Its consistency...
The glutinous rice is chewy.
(Rich in collagen, lotus leaf rice is also good for the skin.)
Dong Hyun.
- Is it good?
- Oh, my.
(The glutinous rice is the best.)
All the side dishes are good too. Awesome.
There are many of my favorite dishes.
Everything tastes so good.
This one is good, too. Try it.
This is amazing.
(Seasoned freshwater snails)
(Humming)
(Delicious side dishes whet their appetite.)
I ate not so long ago,
but it still whets my appetite.
Try this.
It's my first time eating it.
We'll leave before 45 minutes.
(Okay, I got it.)
(He can't stop eating.)
You eat so well.
It's really delicious.
- Let's go now.
- Let's go.
To wash our hair.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
(Team Guys)
Although we got it wrong, we did it as a team.
Put your seatbelt on.
- No stress.
Of course. We got it wrong...
without any stress.
- This is good.
- It's unfortunate, but it's okay.
We probably got it wrong again even if we had a reattempt card.
I agree.
- After answering...
- We had...
all three fingers extended.
(Justifying themselves endlessly)
After winning Yesan A...
(Yesan A: Daeungjeon Hall of Sudeoksa Temple)
We can continue after putting them to sleep.
- Okay.
- We have enough time.
(They're moving after making a simple plan.)
(Team Guys can't get over the shock from Seosan.)
Getting a question wrong could...
make us feel down and lose confidence.
But it's okay.
(Yes, there's stress.)
Let's try to stay positive.
I'm more intuitive than you'd think.
Okay.
I imagine us going to Yesan A...
and taking a lot of time there.
- Then we'll go to Asan.
- We'll also put them to sleep.
I think we'll get both of them right...
and win in the end.
And turn the tables?
I felt some strong positive energy.
What if they also get it wrong at Seosan?
Then we're more likely to win.
I'm sure they'll get it wrong in Seosan.
They'll get it wrong even with the reattempt card.
Whatever the problem may be, let's stay calm.
Okay, that sounds good.
No question would be more flustering than the question about fingers.
Don't you agree?
(Team Handsome)
The hair salon is really big.
Let's go.
(For the shampoo assignment)
(They called and made a reservation at a hair salon in Buyeo.)
Hello. I'm sorry.
Can we shampoo our hair?
They must be startled.
- Hello.
Can we shampoo our hair?
- Where can we wash our hair?
- Over there.
Thank you.
(Thank you for giving us your permission.)
May we use this shampoo?
Hey, Dong Hyun.
- Yes?
- Don't change...
the water temperature so suddenly to tease me.
- Don't do that.
- Of course not.
Don't do anything like that.
- We don't have much time.
- Please do it quickly.
Sure, I'll hurry.
- This is for your neck.
- Okay.
- Is that how you'll do it?
- Or he'll get wet.
Right.
Is this correct?
The towel might get wet.
This is incredible. He put the towel over here.
- It should be around his shoulders.
- Exactly.
- Right.
- This is my first time.
- Yes, I can see that.
It looks like your first time.
Does the water feel okay?
Yes, it's great.
- How long have you been working?
- Today is my first...
- Today is your first day?
- Yes.
- You're working for the first time?
- You must be a part-timer.
- The water is getting cold.
(Clenching his teeth)
To prevent water from getting in the ears,
put your hand behind and block the ear.
- You must be the director.
- Yes.
Cover the ear. That's good.
Be careful not to put water in his eyes.
From the bottom.
That's it.
This is good. You're good.
I did this much.
If you live around here, you should come here.
I'll take good care of you.
Turn the water off to save water bills.
That's it.
Sir, the shape of your head is beautiful.
The shape of my head?
I don't think it's that beautiful.
I will...
- give you a scalp massage.
- Nice.
- Doesn't it feel good?
- Yes.
- This part is very...
- It looks very refreshing.
Don't you usually cover the eyes?
- Actually, - I forgot.
I don't cover the eyes when the client is handsome.
- Really?
- Yes.
They always cover my eyes.
(That's strange.)
Most of the time, they cover my eyes.
The person who shampooed your hair...
- didn't want to see you.
- Is that true?
Do they not cover your eyes, Jae Hyeon?
- I don't think so.
- Really?
- Speaking of which...
- Do you know how they cover me?
They cover my face like this.
They cover me like this.
- For you to breathe?
- Seriously.
- So that you can breathe?
- This is how they cover me.
(Laughing)
- I'm serious.
- Stop lying.
I'm serious.
This is how they cover me as soon as I arrive.
That's hilarious.
- The ears should be clean.
- I see.
Is it done now?
The bubbles are still behind the ears. Is that okay?
- It's fine.
- You're done.
- Please get up slowly.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- The chair isn't coming up.
Wash your hair again more meticulously.
It's okay. This foam is harmless.
(It's time to dry his hair.)
We don't have time for this.
Alternate between H and C air.
- H and C air?
- That's right.
(How cool was that lingo?)
(Patience)
- Sir.
- Should we style your hair?
I'm good, but I can't see ahead.
This is the famous hairstyle from "Star in My Heart."
- The one worn by Ahn Jae Wook.
- Ahn Jae Wook? Okay, good.
- We're done.
- Thank you.
(They're done with the free shampoo card.)
(Team Guys)
There are a lot of people here.
What is this place?
- This place...
- No way.
- It's a village.
- It must be a tourist spot.
We must eat here, guys.
I can sense our victory.
I bet we'll be offered a deodeok set menu.
(Hearty and homey restaurants greet them.)
Don't ask me.
- We're here.
- It's Sudeoksa Temple.
(They arrive at the shopping district...)
(in front of Sudeoksa Temple.)
Open for 80 years.
Wild vegetables bibimbap.
- My gosh.
- I'd go crazy there.
Check that out.
Don't ask me. I was surprised by that restaurant.
(Let's answer the quiz correctly and eat our meal!)
- A pillow that'll have you faint.
- Aster leaves.
(Laughing)
Did you see that pillow?
We should buy one of those.
Pillows that'll have you faint.
That's made for Dong Hyun.
(And traditional snacks!)
We're allowed freebies, right?
Freebies?
- Thank you.
- Me too.
- We're allowed freebies.
- Just the oranda.
- It's good.
- Thank you.
- Try this too.
- We're good.
We shouldn't turn her down like that.
Thank you.
- Would you like more?
- No, I'm good. But thanks.
Wait. Isn't this...
- Take a look.
- Thank you.
Come by sometime.
Yi Kyung.
We're allowed to take freebies.
Well, I...
I won't eat that either.
(Then, allow me.)
Check out this place.
"Mount Deoksung..."
I know what that is.
- "Sudeoksa Temple." - This place.
- It's...
- It's nice here.
Deoksung...
What's the female version of a young master?
Ma'am?
No, that's not what I meant. Young Man.
- Young Man?
- As in Young Man Deoksung.
- Is he a fortune-teller?
- Is he someone you know?
- Do you know him?
- No, I mean...
There's a story about him.
(Lady Deoksung and Young Man Sudeok)
Is it something you read earlier?
I read it earlier, but I brushed it off...
because I knew it.
(He's from around here and must know about Sudeoksa Temple.)
(Sang Uk might play a huge part during the quiz.)
- Right now...
- What was it?
Do you see the water drop of victory?
(The water drop of victory that greets them?)
(The way to victory is giving off a good vibe.)
I can't believe how huge this place is.
The trip back to the car will be just as long.
(It's a long road ahead.)
- I love it.
- Goodness.
You said we had to look at everything.
(That earlier wasn't the actual entrance.)
We have to walk quite the distance.
There weren't any signs.
We're finally here.
The Daeungjeon Hall...
(The Daeungjeon Hall should be here somewhere.)
I'm still going strong thanks to the snacks.
- The snacks?
- Yes.
Do you see the water drops of victory?
Just let it drop on you.
(Water drops of victory greet them once again.)
One got me.
(However...)
(Sighing)
Are you kidding me with this walk?
We should be given a hint for this.
We've been walking for 37 minutes already.
(That's a lie.)
(My gosh!)
Did you see me twist my ankles?
Did you see that? Remember that from earlier?
- The victorious...
- The victorious energy.
- A lucky twist of the ankle.
- That's right.
(What's that? Victorious energy)
This is grand.
We need to walk all the way up there.
(After the third gate, they see another gate.)
(The size of Sudeoksa Temple is out of this world.)
- This...
- I think this is it.
My butt has been lifted from the walk...
and it's almost touching my shoulder blade.
(His glutes are being greeted by his shoulder blades.)
(Coughing)
(Mixed with a cardio exercise)
Very good.
There's a monk.
(Someone awaits them by the fifth gate.)
He's waiting for us.
(Financial Director of Sudeoksa Temple)
(Monk Hyunjoong)
(Panting)
- Sir.
- Goodness.
You're on high ground.
I know it was quite an exhausting uphill walk.
- Hello.
- It's good to see you.
(The monk who will be their guide at Sudeoksa Temple)
- Hello.
- We...
- You must be exhausted.
We'd appreciate...
the sticker.
(Are you heading down?)
He wants a sticker for arriving here.
We should get a sticker for arriving here.
(Just say we correctly answered the question.)
What kind of a temple is Sudeoksa Temple...
and how was it built here?
(What kind of a place is the huge Sudeoksa Temple?)
Sudeoksa Temple was built during the Baekje period.
The Baekje period.
According to documents, Baekje had a total...
of 12 temples.
Sudeoksa Temple is the only one that remains.
(Sudeoksa Temple, the only Baekje temple that stands)
Could we take a look at the Daeungjeon Hall?
Why not? We should go see it together.
- Sounds good.
- Shall we?
I can sense that we'll get a hint.
I have a good feeling about this place.
(Yesan A: Daeungjeon Hall of Sudeoksa Temple)
That is the Daeungjeon Hall.
- Can you see it?
- Is that the Daeungjeon Hall?
Yes.
Gosh, this is amazing.
(National treasure: Daeungjeon Hall of Sudeoksa Temple)
What do you think of the hall?
I can tell that it's old.
- It's grand.
- Of course.
The other buildings are old,
but the colors of the hall have faded.
- It's a heritage.
- The temple was found in the 600s.
Most of the buildings burned down during the Imjin War,
but this remains as it was.
(The only building that survived the war)
They say it was built in 1308.
- Did you say 1308?
- Yes.
The year it was built has been clearly documented.
It's been around for 700 years.
(It's the oldest building in Korea that has its date documented.)
In 1937,
when the building was pulled apart for restoration,
they found the construction plan.
The pillar was set on April 17, 1308.
(The pillar was set on April 17, 1308.)
(Wooden pillars of 700 years)
(You can touch and feel the time they endured.)
- No way.
- It's been around for 700 years.
It was built during the Baekje period,
but the architecture is that of Goryeo.
The unique style of Baekje architecture...
can be discovered.
- It's grand.
- What's more beautiful...
is the side of the Daeungjeon Hall.
(The highlight is the side of the building.)
It feels different.
- That's right.
- It's even grander from here.
Those are what you'd call entasis columns.
They're bulgier in the middle...
compared to the top or bottom.
(Entasis columns)
Doesn't the shape of the roof...
remind you of the Chinese character that means "human?"
- Yes.
- It's called a gable roof.
The front and back of the roof meet in the middle to form a ridge.
It's a very simple style.
They come together like so.
It's elegant too.
It doesn't lack anything nor does it need more.
Exactly.
(Goryeo, 1308, Daeungjeon Hall of Sudeoksa Temple)
(Joseon, 1617, Daeungjeon Hall of Gwallyongsa Temple)
The brackets between the pillars and roof...
were done in a column-top complex bracketing style.
The brackets are only on top of the pillars.
There's what you'd call the multi-bracketing style,
but this is how ours were made.
(Multi-bracketing style)
(Brackets are placed between pillars for a more extravagant style.)
(Joseon, 1666, Daeungjeon Hall Yongmunsa Temple)
(Now, they'll look at the structure inside.)
(In awe)
It's as if wooden pieces were inserted into place.
That's right.
And...
in places that need them, wooden nails are used.
All those centuries ago,
how did they carry the heavy pieces up there?
Back then, this was a project...
of great magnitude.
The space in total is about 162m.
- As in the hall?
- Yes.
Even in this day and age, it wouldn't be easy...
to create something this beautiful.
(Yesan A: Daeungjeon Hall of Sudeoksa Temple)
(Time for Quiz)
In front of the Daeungjeon Hall,
let's answer the question about Sudeoksa Temple.
(What about Sudeoksa Temple will they be asked about?)
I'm not stressed at all.
(They start off with smiles on their faces.)
Here's your question.
This is a word that was derived from Buddhism.
Your head will spin when hungry,
so you eat a little just to stay alert.
The word meant that or the food itself.
What is this that also means...
"dotting your heart?"
- What is it?
- Fasting.
Could it be "simmi?"
What's that word?
Let me see.
Does "sim" mean the heart?
Well, I can't give you the exact definition.
I can't put the meaning into words.
"Simmi."
(It's just a feeling.)
- Is it...
- It's "simmi."
Eating a little bit of food?
Staving off hunger or tasting.
Staving off hunger?
Did you say "tasting" since there were court ladies for that?
Yes, but I kind of ruled that out.
- Staving off hunger.
That sounds decent.
What do we have? Staving off hunger, starting point,
- simmi, tasting.
- Simmi, staving off, tasting.
When you dot one's heart,
you'd go like this.
(Laughing)
- That's why...
- Hence, staving off hunger?
You're no better.
- My battery is dead.
- Is it dead?
- It's dead.
Let me spend some time alone.
Yi Kyung will write these...
- and you should think of a word.
- Got it.
(Leaving the screen)
(Forlorn)
Sim...
No, that's not how we approach this.
That isn't right.
(All that's left is the smartest Yi Kyung.)
is this a Buddhist term...
that everyone would know when they heard it?
- Yes. Everyone knows the word.
- Everyone would know.
I think it's an easy one.
- Yes.
- Right?
Because he said, "Dotting your heart."
But is this a Buddhist term?
Should I explain how I came up with it?
I couldn't interpret "Dotting your heart."
If a heart is "sim," and a dot is "jeom,"
it's simjeom.
But it should be done by eating.
Simjeom to jeomsim as in lunch.
Lunch.
- Lunch makes sense.
- Right?
- I think it's lunch.
- I think it's lunch too.
All I can think of is lunch...
- after hearing that.
- The more I hear it,
it's among the three we mentioned beforehand.
- It has to be one of them.
- It has to be.
But it said to "dot your heart."
- Let's go with this one.
- Yes. I think it's right.
Let's get it and put them to sleep.
And go to Asan to read "the War Diary of Yi Sun Sin."
- Sure.
- Sure. Let's go.
- One, two, three. Lunch.
- Two, three. Lunch.
Lunch is correct.
(Hugging)
(What? Is that correct?)
Jeomsim, lunch, came from Buddhism?
Thank you.
- Was what I said correct?
- It's exactly as you said.
It's to put jeom, dot, in hearts, sim.
Hence, dotting a heart.
We wrote various things down...
and chose it after crossing it off twice.
Hey, Sang Uk. I have a gift for you.
(It's something that dots Sang Uk's heart.)
- It's eojuk, the fish porridge.
- Good.
- Here.
- Are we eating eojuk?
We'll head to Asan after we have eojuk.
Should we to-go it and have it in the car?
You can't do that.
We'll win for sure, then.
We have eojuk in this dramatic situation.
- The Sudeoksa Temple.
(Yesan A: Daeungjeon Hall of Sudeoksa Temple)
(Team Handsome)
(After refreshing shampooing)
- Do you feel refreshed?
We'll go to Seosan now.
How long does it take?
It's 60km away. It's quite far.
- It'll take about an hour.
- I see.
(It'll take about 1 hour.)
If we occupy Seosan,
we'll complete the bingo.
Their cuckoo alarm didn't go off since it did at 12pm.
It'll be over once we occupy Seosan.
It means they got it wrong, doesn't it?
It's highly likely that they got it wrong.
Right?
That means it's highly likely that we'll get it wrong too.
It means the quiz is that hard.
We should have saved a card.
That's right.
In that case, we'd won for sure.
We were about to lose, but now, we're on fire suddenly.
With the multiplication.
Right. That multiplication.
I was so happy when I knew it was multiplication.
I was so happy.
It's like when a good student study hard for an exam,
and he knows all the questions when he gets the exam paper.
He solves them fast.
- This is why people study.
- Yes.
That was exactly how it felt like.
Hey. If we win by completing the bingo,
- we'd win a reattempt card.
- Yes.
- It's tempting.
- I'll win it for you.
(The bingo benefit is tempting.)
I'm confident.
How are we going to use it, though? Should we wait until you come back?
No. I can give it to you.
They only give one card.
You can use it when you're on the same team.
- Right. We can use it then.
- Right.
- We should do that.
- Yes.
By the way,
I'm curious why they're not putting us to sleep.
I know. When we go to Seosan, it'll be over.
Why are they putting us to sleep? It's strange.
I didn't know a bingo game would be this tense.
What happens if the other team is in Seosan when we get there?
- We have to wait.
- Is that so?
Why am I so nervous? It's like the CSAT...
It's like as if I were going to check if I got into a college.
I'm more nervous than when I get a role.
(I'm more nervous than when I get a role.)
(A self-CPR)
Don't stop, my heart.
(They get closer to the destination while calming their hearts.)
That's it.
When we take the curve...
- What?
Are they here again?
They're not here, right?
They're not here.
- They're not here, right? What?
- Are they here?
- No. It's a different car.
- They're not here.
(They were frightened out of their wits.)
Yes.
(Team Handsome enters Seosan.)
It's so cool.
(New sentient beings are here.)
I have a feeling...
- that Dong Hyun will become a hero.
- I love that.
- Pardon?
- I have a feeling you'll be a hero.
The places we're studying for some time now...
are often dealt in the Korean History Proficiency Test.
- Really?
- All the time.
- Right. The Maitreya.
- Silla-Tang alliance and Maitreya.
They are all in the test.
(Surprised)
We have to climb quite a bit.
Gosh. It's so steep.
- Hello.
- I'm panting.
- Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Let me introduce myself. I'm Kim Jae Shin,
a tour guide of Seosan who will explain the place for you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Shall we go and see the Smile of Baekje?
- Yes.
Gosh. How did they break and pile up all these stones?
Hey. I piled up the stones back in Jeju Island.
- Gosh. That must have been hard.
- Gosh. You're amazing.
Where is it? Goodness.
(Finally, it unfolds before Team Guys' eyes too.)
- What is that?
- That's it.
They made it on the stone.
That's...
This is the Smile of Baekje.
This is...
- always on the Korean History Test.
- Really?
- You have a certificate from it.
- The Smile of Baekje.
It's always on the test. Rock Trio Buddha...
The exact name is the Rock-Carved Triad Buddha.
Right. The Rock-Carved Triad Buddha.
- Can I tell you about it now?
- Yes.
This is National Treasure Number 84,
Rock-Carved Triad Buddha in Yonghyeon-ri, Seosan.
This is amazing.
The first one holding a marble is...
Dipankara, one of Buddhas from the past.
They're Triad Buddha of the past, present, and future.
"Maae" means carved rock.
When you go there, you can see they are all falling.
- From the 30 degrees-angle...
- Right. They look like this.
- Like Michael Jackson.
- That's...
Michael Jackson.
This carving technique is called a relief.
It's more protruding than I thought.
- That's it for me.
- Thank you.
- I hope you'll get it right.
Happy New Year. Thank you.
I want to get it right.
It was always on the Test.
Rock-Carved Triad Buddha.
- The alarm went off.
- Yesan A!
- What?
- What did it say?
Where?
(Cuckoo)
- Yesan A!
- Yesan A.
- It's right next to us.
- Where's the board?
- Then, they'll go to Asan.
- Here. They'll go to Asan now.
We have to get this quiz correctly...
- We have to go to Yesan.
- or go to Asan.
Also, before the quiz,
- we have to move back.
- We have to sleep.
We have to sleep.
- Let's get going.
- We have to take a nap.
- Let's go and sleep.
- I was sleepy before.
I dozed off a bit, so I'm so awake now.
It's our first meal.
Eojuk. How tasty will it be?
- Gosh. It's cold.
- First, there's something...
Seung Ho wanted to do the most on the show.
He wants to use the card I picked...
to put the other team to sleep now.
Okay, Seung Ho.
(30-minute nap card)
You're right in front of me,
but I'm going to use the radio.
Go ahead.
This is not the right pose.
It doesn't matter whether they got Seosan or not.
It's right for us to use it now.
We should enjoy our meal comfortably before moving on.
(They use the nap card for a comfortable meal.)
(Crackling)
Producer.
Yes?
Put them to sleep.
(Acting cool)
(A final touch)
You drop it from there to here.
Okay. We don't know what situation the other team is in.
- Cut. Okay.
- Okay.
(They're on their way to sleep.)
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
Why does it have to be now?
There's a brochure.
- You never know. We might get it.
- That's it, Tae Hyun.
You're so wise.
- What would it be?
- Gosh.
For goodness' sake.
Why am I hungry again?
(Each takes a spot while it's cramped in here.)
For goodness' sake.
(We do really take a nap.)
Okay. You'll sleep now.
The problem is the quiz is never from the part we studied.
(The nap starts.)
For goodness' sake.
(The lullaby comes on like always.)
Gosh. This song.
This song is really...
How many times did you hear the song?
- This is my 2nd or 3rd time.
- I'm hearing it for the 3rd time.
Isn't it too cruel I had to sleep 3 times out of 4 trips?
For goodness' sake.
The Smile of Baekje. Will it be "Smile back?"
- What is that?
- The Smile of Baekje.
- The question?
- Smile back.
- Come on.
- Is that the question?
Can I study?
No? He says we can't study.
(Stop studying and go to sleep.)
We're not allowed to study.
- We can't study?
- No.
(Team Handsome falls asleep before they know it.)
(Ringing)
For goodness' sake.
(Someone calls.)
- Gosh.
- Hello?
- Is it okay for you to take it?
- Yes.
(Laughing)
Please hold.
(Please hold.)
Someone called and asked if this place is open on Christmas.
(Laughing)
- Is it open on Christmas?
- It's a real phone call.
- That's hilarious.
- In 20 minutes?
I had a good sleep.
I'm sorry, but the person in charge is not here right now.
Could you call back in 20 minutes?
Yes. Thank you.
Jae Hyeon handled it well.
I thought it was an updated part of the game.
(He finds it ridiculous too.)
To wake us up in the middle of the nap?
I thought it was a new way of waking us up.
- Enjoy.
- Thanks.
You can roll down the curtain.
Ma'am, please get us a bowl of rice.
- One?
- Yes.
When the food is served,
I'll have a bowl of rice first.
Gosh. This is homemade gochujang.
(Getting-ready pose)
I craved chili powder so much.
(Except for some snack,)
Gosh.
(they've been fasting for 9 hours.)
This even tastes great.
What is this, ma'am? Agar?
No.
I craved rice so much.
We need carbs.
(Getting ready to devour it)
Sang Uk, did you order yours only?
(Did you order yours only?)
- Did you want it too?
- Ma'am.
We'll have...
- Yi Kyung.
- I'm good.
One more rice, please.
Will you give one more rice first?
It's because you're athletes.
(Amazed)
It's already good when I only had the rice.
How long have we been fasting?
(The first rice of the day is amazing.)
- Thank you.
- Are you having rice already?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Gosh. This tastes so good.
(Totally satisfied)
Yi Kyung.
It's like pickled radish.
(The side dishes have a crunchy texture since eojuk is soft.)
Yes. It's salted radish.
(The white kimchi filled with umami is fantastic too.)
Does the white kimchi taste good?
(Yes.)
- With these side dishes...
- You can eat rice, right?
Like this...
(I'll have a bite too.)
- I'll have it with just gochujang.
- Yes.
Gosh. The aged kimchi is crazy.
It's amazing, isn't it?
(Even though it's their first meal of the day, they love it.)
Hunger is the best sauce.
Gosh. It's really crazy.
(He's taking a big bite again.)
I'm proud and happy.
(He's proud of the younger brothers' appetite.)
You're amazing.
(I can give you that.)
I can see the presence of eojuk, the fish porridge, from afar.
(Now, it's time to try the main dish.)
I didn't know where the word lunch came from.
Right.
- Thank you.
- Yes. Enjoy.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
(Sprinkled with perilla seeds)
(Rice, noodles, and crucian carp)
(With warm eojuk, you can taste the 3 together.)
(Shall we enjoy it?)
Okay, my team. I was so happy today.
- Let's enjoy it gratefully.
- Thanks for the food.
Let's enjoy it and say...
- no stress.
- No stress.
- Okay.
Gosh. It has rice in it.
- It's even better.
- Yes. It's fish porridge.
(He tries the spicy broth first.)
You should cool it. It's really hot.
(Amazed)
(The base of the porridge is thick.)
It's red and tastes like base...
for yukgaejang or jang kalguksu.
It does look like jang kalguksu.
(It's looks like jang kalguksu similar to yukgaejang.)
After having just the desserts...
(It's so hot that the steam covers everything.)
(They cool it down slowly and eat it quickly.)
I can tell they make gochujang themselves...
because it's so tasty.
(Steaming hot)
(It's even blocking the camera.)
Gosh. It does give me strength.
(Amazed)
Since I'm having it after feeling cold,
- it feels like it's melting here.
- Yes. Seriously.
It feels like my cheekbones are defrosting.
(Their frozen bodies are melting slowly.)
The side dishes taste amazing.
(Amazed)
Both of you eat so well.
(The young ones on each side are fighting hard.)
(He adds rice to it.)
(Slurping)
(The younger ones are serious about eating.)
The two of you on each side...
make me keep eating the food.
Gosh. Is this sakura shrimp?
The tiny shrimp.
It tastes so good.
These pickles are amazing.
(He acknowledges it.)
(The frown of the truth)
(Seung Ho drinks the eojuk without a word.)
Every side dish goes so well with eojuk.
Since eojuk is slurpy,
they serve onions, cucumbers, kimchi, and pickled radish.
All side dishes have crunchy texture.
Right.
(As Team Guys were hungry, they enjoy the food tremendously.)
It's really good.
It's been a while...
since I felt my facial muscles getting melted by food.
(Scraping)
(They finish eating by scraping the last bowl.)
- Gosh. I finished it.
- This was really the best.
- Thank you.
We'll go to Asan.
- "War Diary of Yi Sun Sin." - Ma'am, thank you so much.
(Team Handsome)
(They're in deep sleep.)
(It's been 30 minutes since they started taking a nap.)
(Waking up)
The sleep is over now.
You can come out.
- Tae Hyun.
- Yes.
Gosh. I can't believe I fell asleep.
(Woke up)
It's time.
- What?
- Let's go.
We can do it.
(The older ones are studying hard as soon as they woke up.)
Hey, when you look at this...
Where did you find the brochure?
- But it's hard to memorize.
- Maitreya Bodhisattva...
- Bodhisattva is not the problem.
- In meditation.
Putting his left leg on top of the other.
Gosh. This must be it.
(Team Handsome has a fantastic academic atmosphere.)
You take the Buddha in the middle. I'll take the Bodhisattva.
The one with the ball is Bodhisattva.
We're going all in with this one.
Aren't you going to take the quiz?
- We are.
- We're cramming.
We're going all in for this one.
(The one at the back should gather the answer sheets.)
- Gosh. I don't know.
- We're going all in.
We're cramming.
- Everyone.
- Yes.
I'll give you the quiz.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
(Time for Quiz)
Please.
From now on, you'll be disqualified if you turn around.
- Okay.
- I see.
- Turn and you'll be disqualified.
- Hold on.
The shape of two hands...
of the Buddha in the middle of Rock-Carved Triad Buddha...
- is different.
- Right.
- That's...
- The right hand...
The shape of the right hand means getting rid of...
all fears of sentient beings.
The shape of the left hand means...
granting all wishes of sentient beings.
- Time.
- Okay.
Time. Seriously.
What do you want us to do, then?
Do you want to do the hand shape?
Do it?
Don't tell me the three of us has to do the hand shape.
On the count of three, all three of you...
(On the count of three, copy the hands of standing stone Buddha.)
need to do the hand gesture of the standing stone Buddha,
which stands at the center of the Rock-Carved Triad Buddha.
Hold on. Do we do the both hands?
Yes.
(Team Guys)
We'll go to Asan!
I feel different about eojuk now.
Seriously.
(Amazed)
To exaggerate a little, I enjoyed it so much to the point I got angry.
Even the air tastes sweet.
(Though it was late, it was a satisfying meal.)
Since we're Team No Stress, it's annoyingly good.
That's stressful now.
No stress is stressful.
It's a happy stress.
It's good stress.
(They head to Asan in a good mood.)
Good-stress.
By now, Team Handsome in Seosan...
must be stressed out with the fingers.
They took a nap for 30 minutes.
They must be on their way now.
They're on their way to Asan.
(They think Team Handsome is heading to Asan after losing Seosan.)
I love the nap card.
It's really useful.
We can drag them at a critical moment.
They need to shampoo their hair too.
If they get the question wrong in Asan,
we'll have a nice dilemma.
We can go to Yesan...
or win Asan and finish the game.
Either way, we'll bring the game...
- to an end.
- Right.
Our first choice is to come back to Yesan.
Because there's a key...
but we don't know if we'll get it right there.
- We can't be certain.
- We don't have to...
Sit and wait.
We also have the upper hand when it comes to taking more spots.
(Team No Stress is certain that they'll win.)
I felt the action. The perfection.
(Laughing)
Let's go.
(Will their perfect plan come true?)
On the count of three,
copy the hand gesture of the Buddha statue.
- For both hands?
- Yes.
I should've talked to them.
I know it perfectly.
- All right. Ten seconds.
- Do you know?
- I know it perfectly.
- Jae Hyeon, do you know?
- You have ten seconds.
- Hold on.
Jae Hyeon, please. I should've talked to you.
I mean...
Earlier, we talked about...
the sitting Buddha and the standing Buddha.
I even memorized the positions of both hands.
- The Abhaya mudra.
- Now...
The Varada mudra.
- I know all.
- Do you know what's really funny?
Over there,
I was making the exact gesture.
- The center one?
- Are you serious?
- Over there,
I looked at the statue...
and made the exact gesture.
(Looking carefully)
It goes like this.
Please. Hold on.
- Only Jae Hyeon needs to know.
- Here's the thing.
- The two of us know.
- We know.
- I know exactly what it is.
- I know as well.
But Jae Hyeon kept talking about the lotus blossoms...
- and flames.
- That's right.
- Eating the lotus blossoms...
- He talked about other things.
and medicines...
(Jae Hyeon was more serious than anyone.)
And...
He talked about it continuously as we came up here.
While Jae Hyeon works hard,
- he focuses on the wrong things.
- Please do well.
- Jae Hyeon, this is the last one.
- Jae Hyeon, please.
Jae Hyeon, it isn't that one.
It isn't the one with the crossed legs.
- Seriously.
- It's the one in the middle.
It's so...
- The pose is like...
- Let's begin.
It's very easy,
- It's like shooting out energy...
- Jae Hyeon.
- from the palms.
- You know it, right?
- The thing is...
- Jae Hyeon.
- You know it, right?
- Hold on. I...
- It's a very easy question.
I can't remember one hand.
- Hey! That's the problem.
- Hey!
- Jae Hyeon.
- I'm not certain.
I can't remember one hand.
- I can't remember the right hand.
- The right hand?
I can't remember the right hand.
(He can't remember the right hand?)
- The right hand?
- You can't remember the right hand?
Let's begin.
- That means he has no idea.
- The right hand...
That means he has no idea.
- He has no idea.
- Please.
One, two, three.
- Seriously.
- Incorrect.
- Please.
He's completely wrong.
- Look to the front.
- Please.
- Why? It's over.
- I should've told him.
- He's completely wrong.
- I was going to do that.
- He didn't remember the right hand,
so there was no hope.
- The first attempt failed.
- What?
- Do we get another chance?
- Please look to the front.
- Please. Jae Hyeon.
You saw it earlier, right?
- Forget about the lotus flowers.
- Jae Hyeon.
It was written there. The right leg and the left leg.
It was there.
This is why I have the level five certificate in Korean history.
I memorized all three of them.
I'm serious.
- The first attempt failed.
- Please.
It's time for the second attempt.
- Do we get two attempts?
- Yes.
Discuss it among yourselves and submit one answer.
- What?
- Can we discuss it among ourselves?
- I thought it was over.
- The hand gesture.
- Can we discuss it among ourselves?
- Yes.
- Hey, it's over.
- We don't need to discuss it.
- Can I show it to him?
- Yes.
- My goodness.
- It's over.
(A lesson on the hand gesture)
This is it. I remember.
- Three fingers, right?
- Three fingers.
- Hold on.
- Don't do this. Put them together.
- What's this?
- It's this.
- What? Isn't it right?
- Put them together.
- Hold on.
- The arm sticks to the body.
- Good.
- Take off the gloves.
- Earlier, I was too...
What did you do earlier?
Stick the arm to the body just in case.
Hold on. Are you certain?
I'm certain.
This is the hand gesture we want.
- This is the Buddha on the right.
- That's right.
- This is the Buddha on the left.
- This is it.
- That's right. This is it.
- This, this, and this.
- In that case,
why don't the 3 of you do 1 Buddha each?
- Okay. I know.
- That sounds good.
- Do you know?
- I memorized the poses.
- The Buddha here...
- I memorized them all.
- Tae Hyun, look.
- Is it this one or this one?
It's this one. I memorized it.
- I'll do the pose of this Buddha.
- Then it's this one.
- That's right.
I'll do the pose of this Buddha.
One, two, three.
Smile.
Correct.
I can't believe we did it.
(They recreated the hand gestures perfectly.)
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
(I'm proud of them.)
That was incredible.
- I'm sorry.
- That was incredible.
Look at them.
- I knew that you'd mess up...
- Why?
the moment you said that you didn't know the right hand.
- The right hand was like this.
- It was so simple.
You could see the right hand the most clearly.
But you said that you didn't know the right hand.
- I thought, "He'll get it wrong." - At the museum,
I asked the curator...
- what the Buddha was holding.
- Yes.
It was stuck in my head. The Buddha was holding something.
But you got this question...
- Tae Hyun.
- But you got this question wrong.
- It doesn't matter.
- How did you get it wrong?
- You studied so diligently.
- I...
I'm observant. Earlier, I noticed the elephant.
I'm quite observant. I notice everything.
- He told us not to look back.
- I was so surprised.
It was incredible.
(Cultural assets are lovely when you study it for a long time.)
- Shall we pose?
- Okay.
I don't think I'll forget it.
It was incredible.
(Seosan: Rock-Carved Triad Buddha)
This is amazing.
- We completed the bingo.
- The bingo. Hurry up.
Tae Hyun, receive the benefit card.
- The benefit.
- Tae Hyun.
Let's use it when we're the same team again.
That's right. We should use it together.
Team Handsome completed the bingo and won.
- This is incredible.
- Congratulations.
I want to know who will receive the penalty. Let's go and watch.
- Of course.
- That's the fun of it.
- Jae Hyeon.
- I'll come back next week.
Clear your schedule for Monday and Tuesday.
(Was the sinner promoted to a new regular?)
- Jae Hyeon.
- Join our team again.
I gained a junior.
(They happily set off to make fun of Team Guys.)
Thank you.
I think we'll get a question about "War Diary of Yi Sun Sin."
It could be something else about Admiral Yi Sun Sin...
because he has many achievements and famous sayings.
I think the question will be about that.
(Studying up "War Diary of Yi Sun Sin")
This place about Chungmugong Yi Sun Sin...
is in Asan, not Tongyeong.
He's from that region.
(Not knowing what happened, they prepare for the quiz.)
(They hear the song about getting off work.)
We're in trouble.
They got the Seosan square.
Did they get the quiz right?
- Let's give them a big hand.
- I acknowledge them.
(How did they achieve that feat?)
- A big hand.
- I acknowledge them.
Seriously.
Despite losing, we fought well.
Despite losing, we fought well. Seriously.
- How did they get the quiz right?
- Seriously.
- I think it's impressive.
- I'm curious.
- It's incredible.
- Did they use a reattempt card?
Did they use two there?
Perhaps they had the cards saved up.
They would've had a chance if they had two reattempt cards.
(Team Guys guesses that they used 2 reattempt cards.)
My goodness.
Although I lost, I don't feel upset.
- It's nice.
- The sun is setting beautifully.
The other team completed a bingo for the first time in a while.
(Everything is peaceful.)
What makes me afraid...
is that this beautiful, no-stress team will change...
due to the individual match.
The individual match will change things.
Let's keep things stress-free...
for this round as well.
- No stress.
- Of course.
- Let's smile.
- Okay.
(Team Guys drives as they dream of the stress-free ending.)
(Handsome Guys members gather to determine the 1 penalty-taker.)
All right.
We're here.
- Congratulations.
- It has been a while.
How did you get it right?
Tae Hyun, one, two, three.
(A cute ceremony of the winners)
We acknowledged your victory.
We acknowledged it.
We did all three buddhas' poses.
You knew all the poses.
- Yi Kyung.
- Yes, Tae Hyun?
It's the basics of a variety show.
Memorizing the poses is the basics.
No.
The two on either sides were memorable,
but the middle one's hands weren't. We tried so many things.
Did you fail even when you got another attempt?
We failed even when we agreed on one pose.
We didn't succeed in it at once. It was impossible.
He had no idea whatsoever.
He said that he couldn't remember the right hand.
It told me that whatever he remembered was meaningless.
I thought, "He'll get it wrong."
Did you use a hint card beforehand?
A hint card? We had hint cards,
but we used them up quickly.
- It was strange.
- How funny. Tae Hyun,
- you shampooed your hair.
- What?
I washed my hair right away.
I called right away.
I washed my hair in the neighborhood right away.
There was a reason why we got the quiz right.
You guys saved us.
- We saved you guys?
- Think about it.
We were like, "Why aren't they putting us to sleep?"
After we listened to the explanation,
the production crew told us to come down. We were put to sleep.
Since we had time, we read things like this.
It was right in front of us when we took a nap.
Listen.
(We thought that they'd take a nice nap!)
Look at the first line.
"The right leg rests on the left leg."
"The left hand is holding the ankle."
"The fingers of the right hand..."
I was like, "What is this information for?" I copied it.
So Tae Hyun and I...
thought about the poses.
If we hadn't put you guys to sleep,
- would you have gotten it wrong?
- We would've gotten it wrong.
- It was my idea.
- Seung Ho wanted to use it.
Put them to sleep.
(He did it in a cool way.)
I don't know what situation they're in.
You put us to sleep at the right time.
We shouldn't put them to sleep without thinking.
Today, we were on the same team as Jae Hyeon.
Jae Hyeon ran toward us in the beginning, right?
He's quite competitive.
However, he makes...
so many strange deductions.
(An unexpected charm)
I have a bad hunch.
But there's something nice about him. He doesn't eat.
- They're similar in that sense.
- They're similar.
I loved it.
Usually, he doesn't eat until 5pm in the evening.
(Why is that?)
I worried about it a lot.
I knew that Dong Hyun ate a lot.
I wasn't sure if I should team up with him.
I trusted his level-five certificate in Korean history.
It definitely shined today.
It shined a bit.
If it weren't for him...
- It shined a bit.
- Today...
Today, Jae Hyeon kept saying...
- that we had good energy.
- We had good energy.
By the way, the temple stay...
- begins at 2am or 3am.
- What?
When does the schedule begin?
If you aren't going, you don't need to know.
We need to tell Sang Uk.
Why?
- Sang Uk...
- He volunteered to get the penalty.
- I'm sorry, but Sang Uk...
- What?
- didn't even let us talk.
- He really wants the experience.
"Stay still. I'll take care of it."
He's the son of South Chungcheong Province...
and the youngest member of a good team.
- Yes.
- Really?
Tae Hyun, I know what Sang Uk is like.
He'll leave first.
He'll leave first after saying that.
He'll leave first after saying that. Just you watch.
- Seriously.
- He's right.
- You left first when Jin was here.
- Seriously.
- He left very first.
- He's right.
It'll be strange if I get it right.
(When they had a shoot in South Gyeongsang Province)
(His speed was exceptional from the start.)
(He answered correctly when they had a quiz for a penalty...)
(in South Jeolla Province.)
(He was lucky enough to avoid the 1-6th chance.)
Today, he's determined since he's in South Chungcheong Province.
Shall we begin?
- Shall we do that?
- What's the question?
- I'm so happy to watch this.
- Yes.
- This is so much fun.
- Let's watch.
Among the 3 members, we'll pick 1 member who'll be exempt...
- with the first question.
- No stress.
- Let's do it with a smile.
You're lying.
We've been this way all day long.
- Are you serious?
- We're serious.
You'll yield because you don't care who gets the penalty.
- Of course.
- We'll play fair.
That goes without saying.
Okay.
(If you say so)
Among the nine places we were supposed to visit,
- two places were left out.
- We didn't visit two places.
- Asan.
- Hyeonchungsa Shrine in Asan.
Just two places.
(Asan: Hyeonchungsa Shrine)
(A place that's dedicated...)
(to Admiral Yi Sun Sin's mind and achievements,)
(Asan's Hyeonchungsa Shrine)
("War Diary of Yi Sun Sin" is Admiral Yin Sun Sin's diary...)
(over the course of 7 years from 1592 to 1598.)
(It consists of 8 volumes which span from the Imjin War...)
(to right before his death at the Battle of Noryang.)
(Pilsa...)
(Jeuksaeng, pilsaeng jeuksa)
(Pilsa jeuksaeng, pilsaeng jeuksa.)
(Those who seek death shall live, those who seek life shall die.)
And the Yun Bong Gil Memorial Hall in Yesan.
(Yesan: Yun Bong Gil Memorial Hall)
(Yun Bong Gil Memorial Hall)
(A pocket watch he exchanged with Kim Gu before doing the deed)
(A handkerchief he held on to until the end)
(A seal)
(The place has Yun Bong Gil's mementos.)
("For my nation's independence, I won't fear death.")
We didn't go to those places.
I'll give you the question that would've been asked...
at the Hyeonchungsa Shrine in Asan.
Okay.
The national treasure...
you were supposed to see today, "War Diary of Yi Sun Sin,"
contains records of the war and daily life...
as well as Admiral Yi Sun Sin's emotions.
In particular, he often wrote about his longing for his mother.
That's right.
He also wrote about "Blank" of his generals and subordinates.
- What goes in the blank?
- Let me answer.
- Tendencies.
- Tendencies?
Incorrect.
Let me answer. Love?
Love? Incorrect.
That was a nice answer. No stress.
- It was cute.
- Let me answer.
- Names.
- Names?
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
Physical characteristics.
Physical characteristics? Incorrect.
No stress. I love that we're very calm.
- We're very calm.
- That's right. It's nice.
- Isn't it very serene?
- Yes.
- We played the game like this.
Amidst the calm atmosphere, I'd like to say...
that it's my turn now.
(I knew it.)
It has begun.
I thought we were raising hands.
You're stressed out. Okay. Shall we reset the game?
Shall I give those except for Yi Kyung a chance to answer?
- No, don't do that.
- No stress.
- Sang Uk. No stress.
Let's play fair.
Anyone can see that the competition is fierce.
(Afterward)
Let me answer. Worries.
Yi Kyung. Personal information.
- Sang Uk. Family relations.
- Family relations?
Let me answer.
- Memories.
- Memories?
- No stress.
- "I had dinner with them."
Hold on. Are our answers full of love today?
No stress.
How did you answer the previous questions?
How did we do that?
- It's hard.
- Let me answer.
You can't answer it.
(He shows his desire to answer the question.)
I feel like I'm in their predicament.
- You know, this quiz is hard.
- I know.
I was actually serious about...
- memories and love.
- That's right.
- What is it?
- What's the answer?
I want to answer it.
- I'll message the production crew.
- Same here.
Don't do that. There's no stress.
- Tell me if I'm correct.
- Will we get a correct answer?
(Yearly salary, tastes, addresses, advice)
(Incorrect)
Incorrect?
(Disappointed)
(Monthly salary, people who tormented him, debts,)
(colleagues, strategies)
(Incorrect)
It's hard.
(Focused)
(Tastes, monthly salary, relationship problems, evaluations)
(Incorrect)
- What's the answer?
- It's very hard.
- It's hard.
- I was serious with "Memories."
It's my turn again.
Again?
- Shall we receive a hint?
- Again?
- While we have Sang Uk...
- That's right.
I know the answer,
- but I'm keeping quiet.
- Is that so?
He's keeping quiet on purpose.
- I'll try to answer.
- Okay.
It'll look bad if you get it right.
We'll receive a hint then.
Please give us more details.
"War Diary of Yi Sun Sin..."
contains his thoughts regarding his fellow generals...
and subordinates.
What? Yi Kyung.
- Resolution?
- No.
Isn't it something like that? Ambition.
Strengths and weaknesses.
You got closer to the answer.
Let me answer.
Personal feelings.
(Personal feelings)
I think it's correct.
Incorrect.
(Tae Hyun submits another answer after hearing Seung Ho's answer.)
Did you get it right?
Why is he laughing so suddenly?
(Tae Hyun is correct.)
Seung Ho.
(Me? Why?)
(Everyone is curious.)
- I want to know.
- My goodness.
- Are we nearly there?
- Here's the thing.
- Today, your mind is too...
- Calm?
- No stress?
- Yes.
That's the problem.
Stick to your usual selves. Then you'll get the answer.
- Let me answer. Badmouthing?
- Correct.
- What was that?
Why did you guys come up with the strange concept?
Why did you guys dig your own graves?
- Badmouthing?
- Badmouthing.
Had we been competitive as usual,
we would've gotten "Badmouthing."
Had we been competitive as usual...
- That's right.
- It was hard.
You guys came up with the strange concept today.
They kept giving the good answers like "Memories" and "Love."
- That's right. We kept...
- It was so strange.
- We kept going in that direction.
- Was there too much romance?
I was serious about "Memories," "Romance," and "Love."
- What a strange concept.
- That was funny.
Seung Ho has a good hunch.
- Seung Ho.
- He's good.
- Okay. The last one.
- Seung Ho is good.
Wake up. One of them will get the penalty.
Here comes the last question.
This is from "War Diary of Yi Sun Sin."
It's a doodle that was drawn on the back...
of the Imjin entry that was written in 1592.
That's precious.
- Gosh, what's that?
- That's incredible.
Why did Admiral Yi Sun Sin make this doodle?
I think I know.
Sang Uk.
(Sang Uk gets a chance to answer.)
I think the doodle shows the sea...
and ships.
Isn't it a doodle that shows his plan to destroy all enemy ships?
- A plan for the war.
- Yes.
- Incorrect.
- Is it incorrect?
- Look. There are characters.
- There are characters.
They need to get it right.
Let's show them.
I want to answer.
I'll receive the penalty. Get the correct answer.
(I'll receive the penalty. Get the correct answer!)
I'll receive the penalty.
I'm serious.
I'll be good to Sang Uk since I'm the older brother.
Do you know the answer?
I'm not even looking at the doodle.
(He's innocent.)
(Moved)
If you know, answer right away.
- If you know, answer right away.
- Okay.
I'll receive the penalty.
(I'll receive the penalty!)
(Sang Uk becomes absorbed and makes deductions.)
He wants to say, "Let me answer."
There are many characters for "One."
(Why are they absorbed?)
- They won't answer the question.
- Seriously.
Why are they studying it?
(It's our quiz.)
Chinese characters.
Many of the same characters were used.
Can I try to answer?
- Can I try a random answer?
- Okay.
His signature.
If he signs for ten people...
Yi Kyung,
- you're correct.
- What did you say?
- Yi Kyung, you're correct.
- I said, "His signature." - His signature.
- Is that his signature?
- Are you serious?
Is that his signature?
(Incredulous)
- I said, "The pen didn't work." - Are you serious?
- That's right.
- His signature.
That was my answer.
- Why?
- He was practicing.
That's right.
I thought it was too obvious.
(He didn't think that it'd be correct.)
- Are you serious?
- That's right.
- Is it the correct answer?
- Yes, it is.
- Did he practice his signature?
- He practiced his signature.
In the Joseon period, signatures were used to show...
that the document was checked by the person in charge.
It was called "Sugyeol."
Stamps could be forged easily, so signatures were used.
- So which one is his signature?
- Which one is it?
- Is it his signature?
- Yes.
(Admiral Yi Sun Sin's sugyeol, Ilsim)
Gosh.
Why do I feel bad?
- Why feel bad?
- It's okay.
It's because you don't know us!
Yi Kyung.
You're smiling quite broadly compared to how bad you feel.
I did get surprised.
We were able to get the answer.
It's okay. I live nearby.
But...
(Sighing)
Please give the youngest, Sang Uk, a round of applause.
Yes!
Sang Uk's temple stay! No stress!
No stress!
Temple stays are done to have no stress.
- Right.
- At 3am?
No matter how much stress you have, it will get relieved there.
(I might write a journal like Admiral Yi Sun Sin.)
(The peaceful day comes to an end.)
(Dawn at Sudeoksa Temple while it's still dark)
(Sang Uk pierces out through the darkness.)
Gosh.
(Tired)
The air feels great.
Hello.
(Buddhist meditation)
(A Buddhist practice for one to reach enlightenment...)
(by searching through themself)
It's my first time doing this.
(Cultivating his mind and body through Buddhist meditation)
I saw the hand of the statue as soon as I got here.
I lost because of that hand.
(Today's monk to save this miserable man has arrived!)
(Monk Cho Eun of Sudeoksa Temple)
Hello.
Actually,
we're in the winter vassa period right now.
It's a period when we study zazen and Buddhist meditation...
all day long starting from the dawn of day.
Shall we start practicing this as well?
- I'm ready.
- Right.
This is the posture of Buddha.
It's called the lotus position.
One foot is placed on top of the thigh.
Right.
(Flapping)
(It seems quite awkward.)
Right. Lift it gently.
(The other foot is placed on the thigh as well.)
Try lifting it gently.
This is the most stable posture.
It's the lotus position...
that straightens your spine.
I'm struggling from here.
If you can't do it, just unlock your feet.
(Just unlock your feet.)
You have to sit in a comfortable posture.
Right.
Do you feel comfortable with your posture?
- Yes.
- We'll begin.
(With the clear sound of the keisaku,)
(the zazen begins.)
(Sang Uk closes his eyes and focuses on his inner self.)
(He remembers the past times he promised to have no stress.)
(Laughing)
(However, the moments of anguish came to him endlessly.)
(Keeping his eyes closed)
Yi Kyung.
(Yi Kyung who had called out for love and sacrifice...)
(has also left him.)
(He was full of stress last night.)
(After 30 minutes have passed,)
(the meditation ends with the keisaku.)
End with a bow.
Right.
- Let's move on then.
- Right.
This is the Wanwoldang.
- You see the leaves, right?
- Yes.
Let's sweep them up.
Just do it like this.
So it's done like this.
- Like this.
- This way.
Right.
- Keep them in one place.
- Okay. You should rest.
Okay.
(He works on his own with what he was taught.)
(He sweeps the leaves with the broom swiftly.)
It got stuck.
(He checks the leaves that are frozen to the ground too.)
They go in right away.
This is nice.
(His heart feels refreshed.)
It's nice and neat.
(Feeling proud)
(He puts away the tools that he used.)
(He finds the leaves he missed.)
Why are they here?
(The cleaning begins again in embarrassment.)
(A bunch of leaves)
(This time he works meticulously...)
(without missing any of them.)
You've worked hard, so you should have a cup of tea.
- That sounds great.
- Right.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Enjoy your tea.
- Right.
Thank you.
(He takes a sip of the tea made by the monk.)
Is it okay?
It's delicious.
(A warmth that heats up the body that was cold from the cleaning)
I heard you were the world's best in fencing.
You must've worked so hard to achieve that position.
- It was tough.
- Right.
What was the toughest part?
More than the exercising,
it was tough because of the influence of others.
"You're definitely good."
This is what people think about me.
- These sorts of expectations.
- Right.
Right.
- You receive a lot of attention, - Right.
so I think you'll be going through a lot of mood swings.
- Yes. You are right.
- Right.
The evaluation of the people around you...
or the thoughts that you get from those influences...
feel like reality,
but they are only just the things that you feel.
You can't accept those things to be the truth.
- Right.
- The heart that loves your sport...
can't be damaged.
- Right?
- Yes.
Taking a step away from those things...
and being able to look at them...
is what meditation is.
Right.
At least once a day for ten minutes,
I think it is essential...
to be able to free yourself.
- "No stress." - Right.
I'm trying to think with this in mind.
Right.
But stress will always come.
It's important to let go of it quickly.
It would be great if you could learn to do that...
- Right.
- and put it into practice.
- Right. Good luck.
- Thank you.
It was great to see you.
- Goodbye.
(Year 2025)
(For a greater leap in the Year of the Blue Snake,)
(Woo Sang Hyeok has arrived.)
(Today's Handsome Theme is people of the Year of the Snake.)
(Meet celebrities born in the Year of the Snake)
(It worked!)
(Jin Sun Kyu, 1977, Year of the Snake)
(Yu Ri, 1989, Year of the Snake)
(Jun Hyun Moo, 1977, Year of the Snake)
(We need a place to film this!)
(Should we go to your house?)
(With the bold invitations,)
(celebrities born in the Year of the Snake appeared.)
(Kim Woo Bin, 1989, Year of the Snake)
(Can you put yourself on the line?)
(Starting with Kim Woo Bin...)
(Jun Hyo Seong, 1989, Year of the Snake)
(The Handsome Race full of dopamine...)
(with celebrities born in the Year of the Snake)
(With this energy,)
(let's put things to an end!)
(It's me, Dong Hyun.)
(Who?)
(You didn't save my number.)
(The number you have dialed is not in service.)
(Will it end like this?)
(It can't end like this.)
(I can even call for this guy.)
(How will the Year of the Blue Snake be...)
(with the friends of the Handsome Guys?)
Dramaday.me