Really? He said that?
CHAPTER 50:
A CLASSIC, NOT A CLICHÉ
He really did.
How's this one?
No.
Then this one?
The problem is
we don't know what he likes.
Does he like sweet or sexy?
I think he probably likes sweet and sexy.
He looks kind of greedy, right?
Oh, wait a second.
VIDEO CHATTING
EUI-JU, GO-YA
Huh?
Ta-da.
Are you for real?
Then again,
this won't cut it, right?
Not for our first date.
Eui-ju.
Yes, sir?
Are you free this Saturday?
What does he want to say to me
that he suggested a private meeting
on the weekend?
Oh, my.
So what should I wear?
Why is it still only Thursday?
Why is it still only Friday?
It's finally tomorrow.
Why is time going so slowly?
Welcome.
EPISODE 16
Do you have a reservation?
Yes, I believe so.
What name is it in?
Ga Woo-su.
I don't see one in that name.
Then, Yeo Eui-ju?
Not in that one either.
Then, a table for two, please.
-Yes, please follow me.
-Yes.
-Can I get you some water?
-Sure.
-Please let me know if you need anything.
-Okay.
What do I do? I'm so freaking nervous.
Don't show it too much.
It's not a good look.
Don't forget to order cream pasta, okay?
That's such a cliché.
It's a classic, not a cliché.
Just trust me and try it.
Welcome.
I guess he invited us so we can make up.
I guess so.
Welcome.
You got here early.
-Do you have a reservation?
-Yes, after-school for 12 people.
I don't have one for after-school,
but I have one for Actors' School.
No, after-school. After.
-Anyhow, it's for 12 people, right?
-Yes.
It's that table over there.
What are you doing there?
Look at this place.
Enjoy.
-Amazing.
-Oh, what's that?
-Looks great.
-Thank you.
-It looks so good.
-I can't wait.
You all worked really hard.
Shall we toast?
-Yes, sir.
-Sounds good.
Great job.
-Thank you!
Why are you two so dressed up today?
I know, why are you looking so cute?
It's the weekend.
Awesome.
It's so delicious, sir.
How's the date going? Send me a pic.
Sir, can I have some of this?
-Sure, dig in.
-Yes!
-Is it good?
-I want some too.
Let's get a group pic for the memories.
-Great!
-Good idea.
-Let's do it.
-Yeah.
We have to for sure.
Hey, I'm barely in the photo.
One, two, three.
WITH MR. GA
AFTER-SCHOOL MATH FINISHED
Dong-ju.
Hey, Dong-ju.
What's up?
I can't see.
What?
Take me to the hospital.
Okay, just a moment.
Hey, Gi-jeon. Wake up.
What is it?
Woo-su isn't well.
I can't see anything.
I see you had a full-thickness
corneal transplant in your right eye.
Yes.
The only thing we can try is
a deep anterior lamellar keratoplasty.
This surgery keeps the endothelium intact
while replacing the rest
in a partial transplant.
Hasn't it been ten years?
He's been fine with no after effects.
I know.
I thought everything was fine too.
Why now?
Hey.
Are you
crying?
What do we do with that idiot?
I knew this would happen when he started
staying up all night reading papers.
I just knew it, damn it.
Why didn't he listen to me
and insisted on becoming a teacher?
He had to give up
his beloved research too.
This whole time, I've been terrified
that this would happen.
He'll be fine.
What happened to teasing
and scrapping with him?
You know
how much Da-ju cares about Woo-su.
TREATMENT ROOM 1
-Take him up to admissions.
-Okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What did they say?
You dumb idiot!
What kind of a perfectionist know-it-all
can't take care of one eye?
You had the time and energy
to nag at everyone else
but couldn't handle your one job, asshole?
He gets it too, okay?
I've decided to get surgery.
Will that fix things?
To be perfectly frank,
the likelihood of your eyesight
returning to what it was before
is 50-50.
Your cornea is so thin
that the circumstances aren't favorable.
Make sure you don't push yourself
before the surgery.
Just rest whenever possible.
I'm going to be admitted
while they assess
whether they can do the surgery.
So stop making a scene and just go home.
Let's go get you admitted.
-Good morning.
Good morning.
Mr. Ga is having trouble with his eyesight
and won't be able to come to school
for the time being.
I'll be covering for him.
Let's start with roll call.
Sir.
How bad is it?
What happened?
You once said that if he overdoes it,
he could risk his other eye.
What did you mean by that?
If he can't come to school
for the time being,
does that mean he's in the hospital?
How long is he going to be there?
Don't you have class, Eui-ju?
Which hospital is he at?
Just tell me. You can tell me that much.
Although your cornea is thin,
it shouldn't prevent us
proceeding with the surgery.
After the surgery, the corneal refraction
and others will show improvement.
Hey.
Are you freaking out?
Why would I be?
You looked like you were dying,
but you seem fine now.
Since you're getting surgery anyway,
can't they do an eye tuck too
to clear your field of vision?
There's no surgery for personality, right?
You are freaking out, dude.
Good luck.
See you later, glasses monkey.
You're not wearing glasses.
Later, monkey.
You're okay, right?
Good luck.
We'll head in now.
See you.
Hey, no tears, okay?
Gosh, what a dork.
-What the heck?
-Hey!
Hey, Eui-ju. Where are you going?
What the heck? Did you see that?
He asked me not to say anything
until the surgery was over.
He didn't want to tell you
for fear you'd worry.
He's in Hana University Medical Center.
Fortunately, the surgery
went better than expected.
Are you in any discomfort?
No, I feel fine.
When will I be able to read again?
It'll probably feel a bit uncomfortable,
but you should be able to read
in about a week.
To be able to see without any discomfort,
you will probably need
about three or four weeks.
I see. Thank you.
Now all you have to do is recover.
Eui-ju, you left early without permission.
Two demerits.
Mr. Ga.
Are you okay?
I asked if you're okay.
About that nonsense
absolute-value problem.
My answer is…
a promise from ten years ago.
Are you in a lot of pain?
YEO EUI-JU
My mom said if I get this wrong again,
she won't let me watch Pichi Pichi Pichi.
Hold your fingers out.
To get 12, you need 2 more fingers
on top of these 10 fingers.
One, two, three, four, five…
-Seven.
-Correct.
Don't try to subtract
from the ones column.
Think of it as subtracting
from the entire two-digit number.
Then the tens column is helping
the ones column, like friends.
What a nice friend.
Right.
Shall we solve another one?
Hey, I might just be a genius.
Math is so easy.
Next time I see you,
I'll show you my perfect score.
I promise.
But what did you say to me
when we met after ten years?
Yeo Eui-ju?
-Yeo Eui-ju!
-Here!
Four points, sir.
Four points in math?
You just hate math?
Do you know how hard I worked
to see you keep that promise?
Wow, it seems some people
are just destined to meet.
It's fate.
What?
Nothing.
Never mind.
I remember now.
So you were that cute guy
who was good at math.
Wow.
Now you remember?
So? I bet that left you speechless.
Just a minute.
Then,
since I met you when I was eight,
that means you met me way before Deul-i.
What?
Score one for me.
You really are something.
So,
isn't she coming to see you?
Why would she?
Aren't you two dating?
As if. We're just friends.
I don't think so.
You look completely different
when you're with her.
You smile a lot, and sweetly too.
So you don't smile
when you're with your friends?
I guess that makes sense.
Then, can I
still have some hope?
For what?
Never mind.
Get well soon, sir.
Get out of here. I'm tired.
Yes, sir.
Goodbye.
Eui-ju, can you put this down
before you go?
Sure!
I'm home.
-Hey, Mom.
-Yeah?
-Mom.
-What?
Back in the day,
when I went to the hospital in Seoul,
what hospital was I in?
What in the world are you talking about?
You know, when I went to the hospital
in Seoul back in first grade.
Why would you go to the hospital?
I am a pharmacist, you know.
You've never been sick enough
to go to the hospital.
Yes, I have.
Never?
Never.
Dad, have I never been to the hospital?
Huh?
What the heck?
What was that then?
Was it someone else?
Mr. Ga, at a young age,
you became famous
for being a math prodigy.
CHAPTER 51:
THE NONSENSE ABSOLUT VALUE
Is there a reason
you decided to become a teacher?
Right before the second Math Olympiad,
I decided to withdraw.
Officially, it was because
of my worsening eyesight,
but in truth, there was another reason.
While I was over at the training camp,
I met this friend.
GA WOO-SU
MATH TEACHER, MURIM GIRLS' HIGH
That person overslept
and was late every day.
They were even caught reading comics
when we were solving problems.
Watching them solve problems quickly,
even the ones I couldn't work out…
Bang.
…baffled me for the first time.
That person had incredible intuition
and obviously enjoyed math.
I realized I would meet
many similar people,
and I suffered a crisis of confidence.
I was at a loss about my next step.
After telling people I was dropping out,
I went to the hospital
to have surgery on my eye.
And I ran into a little girl.
When I saw how her eyes shone,
and how she jumped around in excitement,
I was reminded of the moment
when math first sparked my interest.
I had only ever learned before,
and that was the first time I found joy
in teaching someone else.
Then, that little girl
must have gone on
to compete in the Olympiad like you
and become really great at math.
Well.
Life doesn't always turn out
how you expect.
She's lost it.
One final question.
What does math mean to you, Mr. Ga?
TEACHERS' OFFICE
Math…
-Good morning.
Good morning.
Math
is the process
of constantly discovering my own limits.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
I got 55 points.
Great job on making it through
another year of boring school.
Yes, sir, we did do an amazing job.
-Great job, everyone!
-Great job!
-Guys, well done!
-Good work.
-Great job!
Now you're all seniors.
If you spend the vacation chilling,
you'll regret it come March.
I'm not saying
you should do nothing but study.
Take some time to figure out
what you like and dislike,
what you're good at,
and what you want to do.
Check on yourself at all times
and get to know yourself better…
and move forward.
I hope you will walk the path
of your choice with confidence,
regardless of what others say.
You are
all…
stars with your own light.
-Oh, Mr. Ga.
-How sweet!
Class dismissed.
-Thank you.
CHAPTER 52:
I'M GLAD WE MET
-What do you think?
-It's great.
"You and I, our hearts so close."
"Like orbiting stars,
distant for a spell but close for ages."
-What do you think?
-Wow.
Eui-ju, Go-ya.
-You two have talent.
-You guys killed it.
-Props. Respect!
-It's amazing.
-It's so cool.
-I love it.
-The best.
-We did slay this.
"Orbiting stars," that's totally us.
-Yeah, for real.
-Oh, Eui-ju.
I'll definitely come visit, okay?
Make it soon.
Got it. I'll be on the next plane.
Jenny.
Don't forget us.
And don't leave the group chat, okay?
I'm going to spam you
with emojis all the time.
Please do.
Take care, Jenny.
Get yourself a boyfriend
before you come back.
Okay.
What's taking Eui-ju so long anyway?
There she is now.
-Get a move on!
-Hurry up!
You're late!
What took you so long?
Ji-a said…
she wanted to say bye to Jenny,
so I waited for her to get out of work.
Hey, when did I say that?
That's exactly what you said.
Oh, Ji-a.
Ji-a.
I'll never get used to her energy level.
So true.
You guys are like cat and dog.
Meow! Woof!
I'm sorry for not being there for you.
Take care over there.
Here, eat this on the way.
Oh, my seatmate.
-Seatmates.
-Thanks.
Jenny, I got you something too.
Take care and don't forget us.
Okay.
Ta-da!
A STAR FAR AWAY
Awesome!
Eui-ju.
I'm gonna miss you.
For sure.
Hey, I'm over here!
I'm over here.
I love you!
-She's going.
-Bye.
-Bye, Jenny!
-Bye!
I'm glad we met.
Thank you for welcoming me so warmly
and giving me all these special memories.
I'll take a photo of you.
-Good.
-Great.
-Stand here.
-Korea's beautiful.
-I like tteokbokki.
-You like it?
-Tteokbokki is the main event.
-No, it's boring by itself.
-No, that's the best part.
-I like sundae too.
Or what about chicken and pizza?
Oh, right.
As for my novel,
thanks to the supportive readers
fervently hoping for its re-launch,
I finished writing it
and launched it officially.
It hit a million downloads.
I've finally become a mega-hit author.
Oh, you want to know how it ended?
WE WERE FRIENDS, FINAL EPISODE
Fine, I get it.
Now that I've finally realized
that you like Tae-ha,
I'm done.
Si-on.
I said I'd have no regrets.
But I do.
I regret all the cruel words
I said to you.
Thanks for everything, Yoon!
Come on, it's not like
we won't see each other again.
We won't.
Today is the last time.
Is that really necessary?
Si-on, you were my everything
back in high school.
I don't want to lose you.
It definitely seems like I won.
So why do I feel like crap?
You think it's a competition?
So what if you win?
Do you get a medal or something?
You little punk.
Don't.
I'm leaving.
Si-on, wait.
What the heck?
There you all are.
I've been looking for you forever.
Let's all have a seat.
What the heck?
What's with the strained atmosphere?
Did someone die or something?
I'm not in the mood for jokes.
So you got dumped.
You know…
So you're just going to give up?
I…
refuse to give up on Yoon!
Hey, Jae-min.
What? What have you got to say?
Damn it.
Hey, Yoon.
Are you really never going to
see Si-on again?
Of course you are.
You too, Tae-ha.
Can you be happy
when Yoon is so sad?
Let's all move in together!
Huh?
-All of us?
-It's no big deal.
Let's all live together.
You only truly get to know someone
after living together.
That's how
you get to see their true nature.
Still, there's no need
for all of us to live together.
Are you scared?
Then butt out.
Never!
I'm confident too.
This doesn't seem right--
Hush!
Don't worry,
my little baby deer.
What?
This is going to be so much fun.
Fun?
It's going to be hell.
Is this the start of round two?
Okay, let's go!
To our home, sweet home!
Yeah! Bang, bang!
Let's go!
MOST POPULAR WEB NOVEL OF 2026
WE WERE FRIENDS
FINAL CHAPTER:
FIRST SNOW
Honey,
when was this taken?
Oh, wow.
That's when I went to the ER
with food poisoning.
The ER?
When you kept feeding me raw oysters,
saying they were good for my stamina.
Man.
Oh, that time when we were up in Seoul?
What brings you here?
You're leaving tomorrow, right?
Have you finished packing?
Yeah. Are you here to say goodbye?
I'm here to give you this.
I heard hospital bills in America
are really expensive,
and it can be hard to get hold
of medicine. What if you get sick?
Don't get sick.
And don't get too close to Deul-i
while you're there.
Then again, don't get too close
to any American girls either.
Just focus on your studies, okay?
Also,
watch out for pretty American girls…
and handsome American guys as well.
If anyone talks to you,
don't smile back at them.
Okay?
Thanks.
That's exactly the smile
I'm talking about.
This is going to be a disaster.
You're only staying in the US
during the vacation
to conduct research, right?
You have to come back.
Talk about overthinking.
Good luck with your writing.
What's your next novel about?
The title is…
Have a great trip.
Thanks. Look after yourself.
Mr. Ga!
Come here, sir!
Look, it's snowing!
Snow! It's the first snow!
First snow.
It's snowing!
It's the first snow!
Do you like it that much?
Of course!
It's my first snow!
First snow!
My first snow!
-Rock, paper, scissors!
Everything is sweet and sour
This might be the real me
Fill it sweetly
Sweet and sour
-So cute!
-Jenny!
What's really on your mind
If you feel uneasy
You know it's all right
When you look up to the sky
It's sweet and sour
Everything is sweet and sour
This might be the real me
Fill it sweetly
Sweet and sour
-Bye!
THE END
Subtitle: Paul Carver